<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-12-29T20:55:22-05:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Do Magick For Andrieh Vitimus</title><subtitle>Andrieh doing the freaking magick.  Just that.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Day 27 Re-access</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/29/domagick-day-27-Reasscessing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 27 Re-access" /><published>2018-12-29T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-29T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/29/domagick-day-27-Reasscessing</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/29/domagick-day-27-Reasscessing.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.esotericmeanings.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/thoth1_towertarotcard.jpg.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;tower&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;# Tower Card&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A couple days ago, I did a reading and the tower card kept coming out.   Obviously if you read this blog through, that happened.   The tower is not needfully always bad.   Just implies sudden change.   That definitely happened.  Now I have to re-access things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am definitely doing better as far as my emotional state, definitely more strong after the death of my mentor but there is a lot to think about that I have some room to think about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;todays-work&quot;&gt;Today’s Work.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I did 20 minutes of Microcosmic Orbit in a very NeiGong fashion.   Additionally I did some divinations to just check myself before I wrecked myself.   I am going to do some cleaning work ( physically re-organizing space).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;problem-my-eating-has-tanked&quot;&gt;Problem: My Eating has tanked&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the drama and the grieving, I have reverted to some bad habits around food given the stress of the death and bat shit crazy people in my home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;solution-proposed&quot;&gt;Solution Proposed&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting with the my fitness pal app again.  That should shame me enough to get it to work.
This isn’t going to help with the exercise point, that I have to seriously think about how with teaching the classes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;problem-doing-the-magic-has-actually-hurt-other-aspects-of-time&quot;&gt;Problem: Doing the magic has actually hurt other aspects of time&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have done some big lifting but that takes enormous time.  I am well behind on what I need to do for my classes, let alone what I would like to do in my metaphysical teachings.   Going to have to a bunch of cutting.   I mean this was just qigong and then morphed into some major heavy lifting rituals.   That wont be sustainable once classes start again for me&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;solution-&quot;&gt;Solution ???&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No good ones.
Yeah I don’t have a good one for this.  Time management starts to not work when you are overcommitted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;biking&quot;&gt;Biking?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hahahaah it got cold, but seriously, I need to get on the training, but the time is really hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know I a was seriously overburdened before the death, and then the stupid drama.   I probably needed to do the serious cleansing magic to even get to where I could think about the problems and take action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;other-issues&quot;&gt;Other issues&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just cause I got a victory on the anxiety front in the house, although not through the means I wanted but really people were seriously contemplating suicide in the home I own.  They should have been in a hospital, but they would not allow that.  They all needed to go.   Really I was just trying to do Angel work to really spiritually clean the house to give me some space to breath.   There are still issues challenges, and I think that fight with the conceptualization of anxiety as a malignant entity directly attacking is far from over.  At least I have some space to breath as I am coasting into the end of the magical 30.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"># Tower Card</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 26 More Crazy and Purification</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/28/domagick-day-26-more-shit-and-purification.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 26 More Crazy and Purification" /><published>2018-12-28T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-28T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/28/domagick-day-26-more-shit-and-purification</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/28/domagick-day-26-more-shit-and-purification.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.glc.org/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/glc-aboutthelakes-images-erie-large.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lake Erie&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So there was more full fuckery when people were moving today.  Left some nice little curse work behind around by the people leaving.  Realize we didn’t charge them rent.  Fun Times. Endless drama.   Really negative energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So first, I took all the negative vibes, curses and etc and dissolved them in a purification ceremony at the lake.  Dissolving ceremony to pull and capture the negativity and dissolve it in the lake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, I went and cleaned the two rooms with extreme cleansing magic.  There was some complications and it took a lot of energy, but I got everything cleared and did the clearing a few ways.   Made sure everything was cleared and threw away the remaining stuff the people left behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were still hiccups, and you could tell some of the things left behind negatively interfered with some of the people.   Cleared out all the shit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doing the purification rituals inlui of Qigong.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 25 The Shit-wave finally Breaks</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/27/domagic-day-25-Oh-Shit-Social-Breakdown-Resolved.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 25 The Shit-wave finally Breaks" /><published>2018-12-27T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-27T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/27/domagic-day-25-Oh-Shit-Social-Breakdown-Resolved</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/27/domagic-day-25-Oh-Shit-Social-Breakdown-Resolved.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://graduway.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/Good-Bye.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;goodbye&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So a big drain on the positive energy of our household was removed.  We had let some people stay to try to get their life together.   They are gone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They honestly created problems and did so in passive aggressive ways from breaking my space down ( and then playing the victim card after repeated requests to please don’t do that), refusing to energy cleanse themselves, or take any personal responsibility.  Many times they would pass it off like, oh its not us, its the disease but this is just gaslighting and they would ramp that fear and anxiety up in themselves to cause problems throughout the house.  I am very willing to help people but not people who won’t help themselves.   When you push boundaries to cause other people pain, you can’t really claim its just the mental illness sorry, not sorry.  Then they did this over text and honestly the most insulting way possible.   When they actually came, decided to be total assholes to their sponsor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is not how you gain control over your own life without major problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe this is a direct result of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/19/domagick-day-17-Changing-the-dynamic.html&quot;&gt;Angelic purification ritual&lt;/a&gt; based to purify and expel the negative energies in the house ( part of they were causing, part of it was our own issues, part of it was the reaction to those issues).  My intention was not to get rid of them, the intention was to clean up the negativity in the house and try to move everyone forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I did the Qigong and started to reinforce the angel work again to clean up the mess.  They were not able to get the stuff out fully so I expect drama tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The thing is I know there is still problems in the house, but it is less of the anxiety problems and less of the suicidal issues from others bringing real bad shit into the house.   I mean my fight with that &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/19/domagick-day-17-Changing-the-dynamic.html&quot;&gt;anxiety conceptualization&lt;/a&gt;, I can’t fight 5 on 1 with that.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 24 Client Work and More Cleansing</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/26/domagick-day-26-Client-work-and-lots-of-Qigong.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 24 Client Work and More Cleansing" /><published>2018-12-26T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-26T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/26/domagick-day-26-Client-work-and-lots-of-Qigong</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/26/domagick-day-26-Client-work-and-lots-of-Qigong.html">&lt;p&gt;I had to do some Paimon Work which involved creating a talisman to change their influence levels.  I can’t say exactly what was done, but this work was to demonstrate how to do extended drawing or scroll magic.   Yep no pictures again, client work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also re-asserted the angelic purification for the house and doing some Qigong work ( full Chilel set).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I had to do some Paimon Work which involved creating a talisman to change their influence levels. I can’t say exactly what was done, but this work was to demonstrate how to do extended drawing or scroll magic. Yep no pictures again, client work.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 23 Xmas, no Jesus</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/25/domagick-day-23-The-Queen-of-The-West.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 23 Xmas, no Jesus" /><published>2018-12-25T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-25T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/25/domagick-day-23-The-Queen-of-The-West</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/25/domagick-day-23-The-Queen-of-The-West.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/2524/0922/products/Sku_06836_06837-Buddha-Board_99155b23-4173-493b-9f70-6748f02ba284_1200x1200.jpg?v=1516892768&quot; alt=&quot;Buddha Board&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tested Qigong with my student and did a good 30 minutes of macrocosmic orbit.   One of the gifts I recieved was a buddha board.  It turns out this is a unbelievable talisman for spirit work in general, and just kinda cool.    The buddha board actual uses clear water and disappears as you write.   So it has a temporary ink scroll effect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zac and I summoned:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Xi-Wang-Mu.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Xi-Wang-Mu&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;xi-wang-mu-西王母&quot;&gt;Xi Wang Mu 西王母&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;queen-mother-of-the-west&quot;&gt;Queen Mother of the West&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;devourer-of-men&quot;&gt;Devourer of Men&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;granter-of-life&quot;&gt;Granter of Life&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;teacher-of-the-immortals&quot;&gt;Teacher of the Immortals&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a spirit that was bothering me to make contact because Zac had previously made contact but it just didn’t go right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ritual was actually one of the few non-purification rituals I  have done in the last 20 days, although arguably it was empowering.  This spirit is complicated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This ritual was almost purely Shamanic aka just fucking do it, not much ritual, but there were some ritual components.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So first we sanctified the Buddha Board and the space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was pretty sure I understood the spirit from the initial contact the spirit had made with me.  Now, I had very few details about the spirit outside of the name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went into a shamanic trance and started drawing on the board.  The board only lasts a minute, so its phenomenal automatic drawing/writing tool for trance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What did I draw.  Foxes, mountains, even the description as a truly beautiful woman was all right on the money.   I described a spirit that has the keys to life and death and is somewhat detached and humorous about that.   Then started relaying message through the board ( writing them down) and they would disappear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zac did divinations.   Everything was very consistent with historical information of the older versions of Xi Wang Mu, not the newer salvationist narratives.  Then shit got personal, and we tried to do a working directly with channeled energies from the spirit and into the board.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me, this seemed to become a moving spell like a animation as I was drawing it, because the board itself fades, it allows for a sort of moving sigil, or series of temporary&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a very cool experience and meets a lot of where I need to be working right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Portable.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Minimalist.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Essentialist&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now honestly the board disappears too quickly for normal sigil work, or at least you’d have to repetitively draw it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were some issues where the medium ( ahem Zac) interrupted in the spell work.   SO, I had to teach my bro some things about that style of work :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that said,  It was actually a very life affirming ritual ( she has access to the peaches that the immortals eat to become Taoist immortals).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So really the talisman work her was to sanctify the buddha board.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 22 Angel purification launched</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/24/domagick-day-Angel-Throwdown-of-clearing-power.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 22  Angel purification launched" /><published>2018-12-24T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-24T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/24/domagick-day-Angel-Throwdown-of-clearing-power</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/24/domagick-day-Angel-Throwdown-of-clearing-power.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/6/68/Guido_Reni_031.jpg/1280px-Guido_Reni_031.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;St.Michael&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So to deal with the idea of the conceptualization of the anxiety disorder of others as a &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/19/domagick-day-17-Changing-the-dynamic.html&quot;&gt;greater spiritual evil&lt;/a&gt;, I decided to do a more poweful angelic summoning of seven planetary angels&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Saturn    =  Cassiel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jupiter   =   Tzadikiel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mars  =   Samael&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sun   =  Michael&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Venus =  Haniel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mercury =  Raphiel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Moon =  Gabriel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this is a longer ritual and involves blessing each set of herbs and candles with the planetary intelligence, and then elevating like a journey to the planetary archanglel after starting with a planetary gateway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;LBRP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Planetary gateway opening&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Planetary Inteligence ( drawn on candle) and repeated drawn over herbs per planet&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Planetary archangel per planet&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;After 7 planetary archangels are present, call Metatron.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the herbs were blessed, and the candles tied to the evoked angel.   Part of the herbs were used to make a floor wash, part was used to make mojo bags.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was done with drawings on the floor, to make the floor talismanic with the intention to clear all the negativity out of the house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The house was completely rocking and I saw respectible  changes in behavior right from the start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Powerful changes actually. Moving forward on this.  Two rooms of people who were staying with us were actually pretty horrible.  There were lots of problems with them from crossing boundaries, to causing problems purposely. No they didn’t pay rent and we were trying to pay it forward. Completely horrible. New rule, Ill pay it forward from the outside of my house on.  The Archangel Michel got really pissed about how toxic the energy was and cleared it out.  Actually I cried while doing the summoning.  These parties were gone for Xmas.
We asperged the house after boiling blessed herbs together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again major positive behavior changes in .   Good times.  The actual ritual was like 2 hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a couple huge negatives.   It has taken me an immense bit of time to undo and work through the negativity around me that I could see after starting to do the qigong.  This was time I needed to work on my course work at Trilogy for the computer science classes.  I also because of the collective effect of the holiday + negativity clearing have been eating wrongly again.  Yes things are getting better, but its taken a toil to move the dial with the Qigong and purifications.   I have to get a handle on all that.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 20 Microcosmic Orbit and Testing</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/22/domagick-day-20-Switched-to-Microcosmic-orbit.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 20 Microcosmic Orbit and Testing" /><published>2018-12-22T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-22T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/22/domagick-day-20-Switched-to-Microcosmic-orbit</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/22/domagick-day-20-Switched-to-Microcosmic-orbit.html">&lt;p&gt;Today was an insanely busy day.   I had my friend Zac Lui, who is a Chinese medicine expert.  I had him test my progress rehabilitating my energy system after my teachers death.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this is day 20.   He was pretty clear, VERY good progress.   My Microcosmic orbit was strong tight and fast.  It impressed him.  I did this for a good 20 minutes after an LBRP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So he did a pretty through look, thats what he concluded.   Verification of progress.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Today was an insanely busy day. I had my friend Zac Lui, who is a Chinese medicine expert. I had him test my progress rehabilitating my energy system after my teachers death.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 21 Fae Purification taisman</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/21/domagick-day-21-Faery-purification-talisiman.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 21 Fae Purification taisman" /><published>2018-12-21T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-21T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/21/domagick-day-21-Faery-purification-talisiman</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/21/domagick-day-21-Faery-purification-talisiman.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/man-light-people-night-sunlight-morning-639426-pxhere.com.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;purification&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;go-hard-or-go-home&quot;&gt;Go Hard or Go home.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So on line with this do magick challenge, I performed a purification ritual, a much larger Faery Purification ritual with the goal of a creating a greater talisman resonate with a specific type of faery entity.   I will not say much more about this talisman but will say it took me a good 5-6 hours and that was in a DEEP shamanic state, I mean deep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nope, no pictures my friends.  No pictures of my talismans.  I got the talisman done, but its not quite as pretty yet and I need to build a makeshift forge to do this. This talisman is directly related to the post &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/19/domagick-day-17-Changing-the-dynamic.html&quot;&gt;fighting the anxiety demon around me&lt;/a&gt;.  It is purposely attuned to help fight that, and some other issues of a similar to spiritual strenghtening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More details, nope.  Yes they do more then that, but nope nope nope I am not saying.  6 hours of work, not trivial spirits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Noticeable effects, on certain targets.  Yep…  They are shy spirits, cant say more.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 19 Qigong Qigong and Angels</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/21/domagick-day-19-its-a-blur.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 19 Qigong Qigong and Angels" /><published>2018-12-21T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-21T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/21/domagick-day-19-its-a-blur</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/21/domagick-day-19-its-a-blur.html">&lt;p&gt;So on day 19,   I did some Michael and Haniel work respectively  ( Venus and the Sun) to start refocusing and detailing, and turning things around.  So this was a continuation of the expression of conceptualizing some of the issues as external entities from &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/18/domagick-day-18-Every-Day-1-Step.html&quot;&gt;previous days&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started by blessing some every day items, and doing some some Qigong to build energy before doing anything else.  Then rolled into the angel work on the points, carving out some&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, this combination definitely seemed to work although there was some push back it on some of this, but there was most certainly progress that was visual and tangible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very much so, very much so.   Some reactions, some pushback, but tangible progress.   The Qigong, helps to ground and build earthy based Qi before doing the more cerebral energy work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this conception of some of the issues as a foreign malefic agent gives me some tools that are working to make progress.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">So on day 19, I did some Michael and Haniel work respectively ( Venus and the Sun) to start refocusing and detailing, and turning things around. So this was a continuation of the expression of conceptualizing some of the issues as external entities from previous days.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 18 - Every Day 1 Step</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/20/domagick-day-18-Every-Day-1-Step.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 18 - Every Day 1 Step" /><published>2018-12-20T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-20T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/20/domagick-day-18-Every-Day-1-Step</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/20/domagick-day-18-Every-Day-1-Step.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://encrypted-tbn0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcTB7Vt7oA8oKr_rmam0kpD2d5V0YjSXubk3I2TVE94I9Ligg-Qs&quot; alt=&quot;fish organizing&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;one-change-per-day&quot;&gt;One Change per day.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After my longer &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/18/Changing-the-dynamic.html&quot;&gt;post yesterday&lt;/a&gt;,  I realized too, that I can’t just do Qigong outside where I am staying and it will get better.  This does not fix any of the causes.  I realize pretty outright, that any changes I might try to make will be seriously contested.  Re-framing the overwhelming anxiety as a malevolent and entropic force, allows me to direct my anger at that force, not the people.  This is a major shift in conceptualizing the problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I fully expect to get outright resistance, passive resistance, broken stuff and more emotional whiplash as I push forward, but conceptualizing the force in this way allows me to show compassion towards the people and yet stand my ground.  I know this will be difficult, but conceptualizing the people as under the influence of a powerful being, lets me absolve some of the inter personal issues involved and take magical action against that being and not the people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is almost always the track you have to take, if you are doing healing magic with anyone who identifies with the disease egregore but has tried to get healing.  Once you loose the detachment, loose the ability to conceptualize the disease or spirit as separate from the person, you are really actually losing the fight to make anything better in the situation.   Step back, get outside help for perspective.  Stupid fae spirits had to do that for me again.. hahah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is this a sleight of mind, you bet your ass it is.&lt;/strong&gt;   Sometimes a useful remapping is better then the truth which is largely a lie too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, I did make a request to change some components of the environment, I believe the request will help all parties.  I do not know if the request which was made in a very business yet positive way will go over well.  Remember, social unpredictability is part of the “conceptualization” of the powers of the spiritual  malignant opponent.  Unpredictability is a means to take power over the social reality, and it further creates a cycle of anxiety.   I would expect a fair amount of resistance and I have some alternative solutions if it becomes an issue, but I will be taking the one step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And thats the lesson.
Other peoples inner demons and pain will infect you and consume you, manifesting in totally different ways once they get inside you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to remember, you can only take and secure one step at a time when making things better.   Not all of those steps will be doable in the time frame you would like.  People will resist and fight for the status quo, sometimes with great vigilance.  Be stronger, more patience and kinder then the resistance of the pain.  Can’t do something one way, do it another.  Can’t change the physical reality because of the status quo, call on spirits to help clear some of the pain.  Try again.  Repeat.  Analysis.  Find the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh yeah,  I did the Qigong today, again outside ( over by my work) but I did get some coffee after.
Haha, Also did the object concentration ( later at night).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>