<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-12-12T21:34:40-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Do Magick For Andrieh Vitimus</title><subtitle>Andrieh doing the freaking magick.  Just that.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Day 9 - Evocation part 2 with some meditation</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/10/domagick-december-day9-evocation-work-day-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 9 - Evocation part 2 with some meditation" /><published>2018-12-10T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-10T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/10/domagick-december-day9-evocation-work-day-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/10/domagick-december-day9-evocation-work-day-2.html">&lt;p&gt;This was one of those, shit got real days.  This is a second day of working with in ground talismans to calm down some waves of just anxiety and bullshit.  Sometimes you got to work the external to change the internal.   SO again, no Gigong  :(&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intially this is not a fail for this challenge, as I was doing greater purification external work and that really means it fits within the scope and I intially said, do what you got to do on this.  Have a problem with that $$@@# off..  ok its not that serious.  I did a 2 hour ritual stint of enviromental purification.   This is one time that I will just say, I am leaving it unsaid.   Zac Lui can confirm the work (as per the in person verification of actually doing the work), and I will leave it alone from there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will say very fried after two days of ritual work.  HAHAH.. happens.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This was one of those, shit got real days. This is a second day of working with in ground talismans to calm down some waves of just anxiety and bullshit. Sometimes you got to work the external to change the internal. SO again, no Gigong :(</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 8 - Evocation and Qigong with some meditation</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/09/domagick-december-day8-more-evocation-work.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 8 - Evocation and Qigong with some meditation" /><published>2018-12-09T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-09T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/09/domagick-december-day8-more-evocation-work</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/09/domagick-december-day8-more-evocation-work.html">&lt;p&gt;Well, shit I had to do some evocation of a fairy nature.   This tends to be how it goes, I put off a whole bunch of magic and had to catch up on it.  Fortunately, fairy magic rarely tends to further drain me, although I did not want to really take away from the body alchemy and Qigong work, but will have to the next couple days unfortunately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did do the Gigong work as well and did do some object concentration in addition to the magic.  I am still seeing some weird social impacts (fallout really).  Going to add some deep meditations not just object concentration to the list.  Divinatory meditation and readings ( not just divinations), since the work is raising some questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The work I did do which involves an in-place talisman already placed in the ground…  Shit was powerful and strong, and left me completing feeeling astrally burned.   Fun times right !!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was definatelly awake.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Well, shit I had to do some evocation of a fairy nature. This tends to be how it goes, I put off a whole bunch of magic and had to catch up on it. Fortunately, fairy magic rarely tends to further drain me, although I did not want to really take away from the body alchemy and Qigong work, but will have to the next couple days unfortunately.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 7 - Hahahahahahahahahahha moving on</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/08/domagick-day7-hahahahah.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 7 - Hahahahahahahahahahha moving on" /><published>2018-12-08T02:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-08T02:35:37-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/08/domagick-day7-hahahahah</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/08/domagick-day7-hahahahah.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://media.giphy.com/media/DeJ2ifS2V2zlu/giphy.gif&quot; alt=&quot;AHAHHA&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-art-of-war&quot;&gt;The Art of War&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I posted this on my facebook page yesterday:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I match witchcraft of the mouth ( mostly false gossip intended to harm) with actual witchcraft, and I am pretty good at that actual magic stuff. Just be a better person, if you have a problem with me, let’s talk over coffee or something. I am generally reasonable even if I am the wronged party, and pretty forgiving. This is true not just for me, we can make things better for each other by stopping others who are doing this and just telling them.. Knock it off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not a few hours letter I felt a little impotent annoyance.
After 3 independant readings, from people who did not know what really was going on … all three strongly said the same thing, someone tried ( and failed to “curse” me).  I really expected it and was ready.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All I can say to that is 
	&lt;strong&gt;Hahaahahahahhahaahahahhaahahahahahahahahahahahahaahahaha&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good luck, you’ll need it.  Nice to be right about things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moving on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;there-is-only-information&quot;&gt;There is only Information&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So this spellwork curse was an interesting effect.  It did not get through, but it did ping the shields.  Now at the time I got a little subconsiously confused.  I actually lost my balance a little because I lost track of which body it actually was going torwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is good and bad.  It does mean that the Gigong and HGA work is working.  A clear seperation between the astral body and physical is useful in every day life, but it also impedes body alchemy.  Body as talisman right.   This implies my conceptualization is very good, but while most spiritual experts will tell you this is a great thing, and it is…. it does affect your ability to ignore negative ( to you), energies.   Integrating mind, body and spirit in this way is very much a great way to live, but… it negatively affects your ability to selectively pay attention to what you are doing.  That can increase with focus exercises, but it turns the spiritual world up as well as the body intuition.  These   on the surface is all good, until you have a deadline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Western culture ( probably all culture but I will leave that alone) is really based on the denial of spiritual intution, and moreso compliance.   In more recent times, I think very few people are doing anything remotely close to what they would like to.  Jobs even connections to other people, interactions, etc… all lack substitive meaning.  Once you start doing these excercises, those tiny voices that say you should do something different… Well at least for me, they get louder.   Do the work more, the harder it is to ignore.    That brings other inner fears and demons up that you have to deal with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you ignore curse work that “sticks”, or entropic elements around you, yes it tends to cause downward spirals that manifest in behavior and social realities first.   In this case, the interesting thing is that I physically lost balance… a hugely kinetic insight.   Now, I am dealing with Grieving, and shit so its not surprising. What is surprising is that it was crossed cued so far into body sensations, due to the gigong work .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;actually-did-talisman-work&quot;&gt;Actually did Talisman work&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I opted out of the Gigong work today, but did actual talisman work of a purification nature.   With some spell work coming up that way, I did some evocational work, to take care of the problem described above.  This will relate to Qigong, I promise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this evocation is with a set of powerful non-book spirits that could only be described as “alien”, possibly cthulean ( but they aren’t from that paradign).  They are really not intelligent and really are mission focused ( almost can do nothing but eat).  These spirits are also verbally un-named.   So what is outlined is a kinetic seal for the spirit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evocation was as per &lt;a href=&quot;http://andriehvitimus.com/shapeshift&quot;&gt;my shapeshifting course&lt;/a&gt;, and Hands on Chaos Magic.  These are things I have a long term relationship with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every spirit has a internal representation that arises from the interaction between you and it.  Some spirits will resist both a seal to call it, and a form in visual sense.  In fact, a spirit which resists conceptualization are far more difficult spirits to deal with.   That said, it is impossible to resist having at least a kinetic set of “effects”.  Your body will react at least.  If it didn’t, there really isnt even a real way that the spirit is interacting with you.  Your body most at least react in some way, as this is some sort of hook into the subconsious mind.  It is easy to ignore these reactions, but for these type of alien spirits, its critical.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now Qigong actually teaches you in a classical sense, to actually pay real close attention to those body sensations, and then basically try to map out energy blocks and some body sensations to ill-adapted energy.  That is a gross high level overview.  If you are working in that way, it is not so hard to map up alien energies and then when you have a working map, summon something only with the set of “reactions”.  As you move forward in working with an Alien spirit from the “outer” whatever, you just build a interface internally. We can call that a relationship, but with things that don’t classically allow themselves to be anthropormized, relationship implies way too much humanity.  Interface is better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/interface.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Interface Process&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So you have kinda a process to interface building.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Body Reactions, possibly other sensations accross multiple sensory channells to a presense.  Write them down.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Banish each time.  Throughly.  Take accounting of your personality, and anything that happens.  This is risky magick.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Repeat sensations in meditation through submodality work, till you have “pressence” present.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Try to repeat these excercises until you can get some sort of real-world validation that the presense is not just a servitor or thoughtform.  That hardly matters, as a thoughtform can be quite effective… but if something is clearly not a thoughtform, and clearly alien in nature… EXTRA care needs to be taken, especially if it resisting changing its energy&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HINT:  you can usually change the sensory information a thoughtform produces in you, thus changing the thoughtform… it should change the thoughtform.   Spirits of note and alien, will resist this type of change.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;As you work through the interface with a spirit, you should increasingly build an understanding of it, and it should increasingly be able to get real world results on the point that the spirit can work on in this world.  That may be highly limited and specific, as alien shit does not really know about the human world much.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like advanced Qigong, or even Taosist fuckery of a non-dogmatic sort, it is. Although this is not Taoist sorcery of the sort commercially sold and mass marketed.  Its in my shapeshifting course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this case particularly, the spirit was sent to clean up and just eat any negative spellwork lingering out there that just bounced off me, and continue to eat whatever it wants from there that is still tied to the negative spellwork at me.  So if a person is a sloppy magician throwing curses, well you can kinda get what this would do.  Oh did I menion, for the stalkers out there throwing down, the alien thing in this case does not particullar care what energy it eats, so a banishing ritual will just give it more “energy” thats connected to the original curse work once it locks in.   As I said. &lt;strong&gt;hahahahah, Good luck&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This spirit has been trained through the interface to actually only respond to talismans where the blood matches my blood, and only to where the blood on the talisman is the same as the person who is making the request.  Think of this as a double authentication key, mostly cause I dont want an alien intelligence of a entropic and alien sort, connected directly to my body Chi and thus mucking about about my subconsious mind.   Instead, I have to have a talisman with a double blood key and no other simulation of sympathetic links can work.   That’s a relatively anal spiritually secure talisman link, beyond what is probably needed 99.9999% of the time.  I am just thorough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, almost immediately after sending the spirit with a second curse which will go unmentioned, I felt alot more clear headed about what to do where on social fronts.   The real reason this is all confusing, is simply there is alot of &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/04/december-talismans-day-2.html&quot;&gt;dead tissue to clear&lt;/a&gt; out from these fronts. I have trained this alien intelligence to also via the methods above, to carry other curses while its feeding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now just because I have a interface with these kinds of monsters.  I still sat down, banished, and did a full 30 minutes of Object concetration and meditation to freaking insure my subconsious mind was cleared out.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 6 - Working Hard after Work</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/07/domagick-day6-working-hard-combining-tools.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 6 - Working Hard after Work" /><published>2018-12-07T02:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-07T02:35:37-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/07/domagick-day6-working-hard-combining-tools</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/07/domagick-day6-working-hard-combining-tools.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/qigongFeature.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Qigong&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I did A few things.   First my Bro jason was around and he did some Qigong but this was wrapped inside a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sacred-texts.com/bos/bos026.html&quot;&gt;LBRP&lt;/a&gt;.   By wrapped inside, I mean we would go through the angel projections, the kaballistic cross, and after you have asserted the connection to Goddhood, but before a clossing Kabbalisrtic cross.  We were again using Luke Chen’s Chilel Pull chi up and down method.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jason was saying he felt like he was having kidney stone problems right before we started.   After the set, with the additional Angel support, he was so so impressed by this combination, that he asked for a video set of the Chilel.   He said after we were done with the Gigong and the medtation work, he didnt feel like the kidney stone was just dissloved out. Enough so that hes going to try some more.   This combination is something I tried before and it does seem to multiply the effectiveness of the Gigong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We did the full set and then did straing up object concentration work.  I 	am starting to work out some additional helpers for the health kick ( including starting some gym work and revisiting the my fitness pall apt).  Going to switch to the 8 cade brocade soon.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 5 - Domagick, more bad social news, reflection</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/06/domagick-day-5-december-reflections.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 5 - Domagick, more bad social news, reflection" /><published>2018-12-06T02:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-06T02:35:37-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/06/domagick-day-5-december-reflections</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/06/domagick-day-5-december-reflections.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/punches.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Punch&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;chop-wood-carry-water-in-the-underworld&quot;&gt;Chop Wood Carry Water In the Underworld&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes Qigong is not trivial, its just not and it has weird affects as you get better at magic and the spiritual stuff.   So in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dropbox.com/s/bz8yd6xux41vjf4/11-14-2018-Death%20to%20Andrieh%20Vitimus.md?dl=0&quot;&gt;this article&lt;/a&gt;…  In this article, I was basically ruminating that I was still in the Eye of Shiva.  What I mean by that, is that everything is kinda destructing around me.  That the funeral caused me to be so overloaded with death energies that, more or less, it was going to take something with it, and posited that it is a magical name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I am seriously energy compromised, I am seriously not social.  Introvert by nature, but I have felt particuarlly like my whole social reality isn’t working for me and its not really clear what/when/how to change that given my time constraints ( 2 jobs).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since yesterday, I had one social contact(who is basically, pretty popular person), basically all but declare war on me.. not so directly, obviously, they know in a pound for pound magical “issue”, I would put them in the grave or worse magically speaking since I do not stop or take any prisoners, but their intention was pretty clear.   If are the person reading this that this is true, better believe it and I do not have any sense of mercy or restraint on this.   I am shit public figure actually.  I know that, I really need alot of help with that actually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I am actually a really dangerous magician.  Then I had a second friend sort of student kinda also disrepect me, and worst they probably didnt mean it.  Same day.   Kinda fucking hurt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are not things I brought on myself, not directly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I was trying to lay low, obviously since if you have been reading, I have been fucking morning for real&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;and I am just getting out of an MBA program and teaching Computer science now.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;or-did-i-bring-it-on-myself&quot;&gt;Or did I bring it on myself?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are an experienced magician, Qigong does not quite do what you might think.  Qigong by itself is enough to start shifting reality if done with sincerity.  By sincerity, clear focus, good signal, augmenting it with the 5 senses, basically everything covered in &lt;a href=&quot;http://andriehvitimus.com/shapeshift&quot;&gt;my shapeshifting course&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the eye of Shiva, that which remains is truth.   Think about that. EVerything else gets destroyed, except that which is truth.  We can argue about what that is too.. with pratical magic.. no  it does not need,  On &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/04/december-talismans-day-2.html&quot;&gt;Day 2&lt;/a&gt;, I literally did a working to Shiva so this should not be surprising.  I am not really suprised.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As within, As without&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is as you changed the inside you must change the outside.  Change the outside, you change the inside.  Qigong clears the inner energy from dead enegeries, and thus the universe just clears out the dead material and in this case that means social.  Death takes the weakess tissues or weakest parts of your reality and claims the sick parts first.   For me, that definately is the social reality and definately peopling under stress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So with that setback, I have to re-think things.   How do I create, not just let things get destroyed on this front.  Maybe its just a matter of clearing out the bad energies, letting shit go, and then rebuilding.   But it still hurts a bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So will do the Gigong today, and do some meditation.. object concentration.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 4 - Domagic… just doing a movie</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/05/domagick-day-4-december.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 4 - Domagic... just doing a movie" /><published>2018-12-05T02:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-05T02:35:37-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/05/domagick-day-4-december</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/05/domagick-day-4-december.html">&lt;p&gt;
    Well the movie says it all right.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;https://andriehvitimus.cdn.vooplayer.com/assets/vooplayer.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;iframe allow=&quot;autoplay&quot; class=&quot;video-player-container vooplayer&quot; data-playerId=&quot;MTE1NTY3&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; style=&quot;max-width:100%&quot; name=&quot;vooplayerframe&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot; src=&quot;https://andriehvitimus.cdn.vooplayer.com/publish/MTE1NTY3&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Well the movie says it all right.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 3 - Domagic… not very exciting</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/04/domagick-day-3-december-3.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 3 - Domagic... not very exciting" /><published>2018-12-04T02:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-04T02:35:37-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/04/domagick-day-3-december-3</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/04/domagick-day-3-december-3.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;fed-the-spirits-and-did-the-work&quot;&gt;Fed the spirits and did the work.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well I fed the spirits, did the Gigong, meditated.
Was very very tired today… and its still 1 when I am starting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Probably not the most exciting magic, but alas at least I am trying.   I have been thinking I need to do alot more talismans to destroy… or linking items and embuing those items to clear things out.   I will add more later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did not fix the programming issues, so this is still broke ( at least in part )….   Keep on keeping on.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Fed the spirits and did the work. Well I fed the spirits, did the Gigong, meditated. Was very very tired today… and its still 1 when I am starting.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 2 - High Weidness today/Fire Alchemy!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/03/december-talismans-day-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 2 - High Weidness today/Fire Alchemy!" /><published>2018-12-03T02:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-03T02:35:37-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/03/december-talismans-day-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/03/december-talismans-day-2.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;day-2-high-weidness-today&quot;&gt;Day 2, High Weidness today.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/3/34/Camp_fire.jpg/1584px-Camp_fire.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fire&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;opted-for-a-big-fire-ritual&quot;&gt;Opted for a Big Fire Ritual&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In lieu of Qigong, I did a large fire ritual over several hours.
There was tremendous oddities on multiple aspects of the work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a release and dissolve ritual under Shiva, and roughly would be a homa (without the formality).  I had many old ritual remains and herbs and I had No fucking idea what they were for.  They were not labled.  So I through everything into a fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me say, I got some push back right away on many fronts including the weather, but let me say, no I wont be asking for permission to do anything I need to, as far as removing things that seem like life blocks and stagnent energy from herbal mixture/ritual remains that not only were unlabled but were definately feeling stagnent.  End Sto&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-fire-that-wasnt&quot;&gt;The Fire that wasn’t&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When weird shit happens, especially with fires, I pay attention.  I am tryting to write a book on this.  I could not, could not light the fire.  Not at all.  I tried and struggled with this for 2 hours chanting the Ganesh Mantra “Om Ganapataye Svaahaa”  after formally blessing the fire and even asking Agne for help.  Got it to smoke and thats that.  Now there was a lot of herbs in there and there was some other ritual remains.  I took this as real bad sign that shit was way more blocked up then it should have been.  I probably made the fire wrong too and I had decided to do this fire ritual instead of taking a bike ride ( Not sure I made the right decision).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I acknowledged, just that fuck.   I can’t even get the fire going, the obsticles must be much worse then I thought.  My energy was a little more stagnet and the shit I was trying to release EVEN worse then I thought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its just information, right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;then-the-oddity-occured&quot;&gt;Then The oddity occured.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So the fire was fucking out.  I mean fucking out.  Sure it was smoking with some embers, but it was out.   I was sitting and thinking, like fuck… fuck.. and thinking ok.. one step at a time. And then….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the wind literally shifted&lt;/strong&gt;
I wasn’t even looking at the fire, I had already given up, and there was a fire.  Roaring fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Understanding, that this was indeed divinity stepping in, I immediately started doing the Shiva work.  To make the point even more clear, it started RAINING right as the fire kicked into overdrive from nothing.  Can’t get any clearer then that.  I mean the fire went from nothing, to rain can’t touch me within the span of, maybe 30 seconds.  It was simply not possible for what occured without … ehem &lt;strong&gt;magic&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;we-got-your-back&quot;&gt;We got your back.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I comtemplated this, all I could think about was the idea, that the spirits did have my back.  Really.  While I might not be able to make the lift needed to do the sorcery in this case, they were going to do it from the divinity aspect.  So while there was a ton of blocks, shit worked, casue they helped me.   It was honestly a thing I needed, somewhat having fallen into a existential Nihilism mentality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lots-of-mantras&quot;&gt;Lots of mantras&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I did not have a mala, but I did alot of mantras ( Om Namaha Shivaya).  I clearly heard and understood that what I was asking for 
** the destruction and dissolution of harmful stagnet energies **
was actually being granted.&lt;br /&gt;
In the eye of Shiva, only that which cannot be destroyed remains, and what remains is truth,,,, hahah  ;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a while, I was told to go take care of the things I needed to do in daily life, which was mostly making people food.  Shit did feel different, although not sure.  Energetically, I do feel like alot of stagnet energies got blasted.  Clearly these were a type of talisman destruction, kinda the opposite of the challenge, but whatever… I did something yo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;post-ritual&quot;&gt;Post ritual&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I felt like a large weight removed, but then I still got bad news later in the night which wasnt so bad, but just a sort of trigger, when I was already fried.  Thats a real big problem, although I didn’t fix this website, and I didn’t work on the Comptuer science class I am teaching and was not feeling so good ( so I had to cancel a reading).. I should have worked on more, but what are you going to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I need to start scheduling book time, and more writing time, but alas, 2 jobs is fucking brutal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;before-sleep&quot;&gt;Before Sleep&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did do the object concentration before sleeping ( 10 minutes, with 2 sets of 5).  I am going to try to do more than this.  I am actually finding that it is not so much a focus issue, but physical pain issue.  To that end, I know…  I have to do a more formal plan to somehow fit more excercise in, get to a Chiropractor, and do what I need to.  Going to spend some meditation time, planning that out entirely!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Day 2, High Weidness today.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 1 - Do Magick for December 2018/ Cleansing rebuilding!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/02/domagick-day-1-december-talismons.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 1 - Do Magick for December 2018/  Cleansing rebuilding!" /><published>2018-12-02T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-02T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/02/domagick-day-1-december-talismons</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/02/domagick-day-1-december-talismons.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;domagick-day-1&quot;&gt;Domagick Day 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Day 1, December 9, 2018&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;prework&quot;&gt;PreWork&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I decided to ha ve a few harder things with this.   I’ve had alot of death energies around me. &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dropbox.com/s/rd4eblp1oa0advu/starting.md?dl=0&quot;&gt; You can read more about that here &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dropbox.com/s/bz8yd6xux41vjf4/11-14-2018-Death%20to%20Andrieh%20Vitimus.md?dl=0&quot;&gt; More changing&lt;/a&gt;  These are unfinished.   But I kinda decided to just do things in markdown or start coding..   No wordpress nothing like that.  &lt;a href=&quot;http://google.com&quot;&gt;http://google.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Straight only code I develop myself.  Yes oddly this is part of the talisman work.  Reconditing a skill set and accepting it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The plan is to work to get on the excercise program more throughly… Start with 1 Gigong a day and move up to 3-4 sets of gigong a day ( thats only like an hour) with a whole bunch of escalating excercise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortantely for me. I have 2 jobs now ( and one job is very time consuming), it is teaching computer science classes and my day job.   So very little time…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;you got to work with what you got&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;checking-in-with-myself&quot;&gt;Checking in with Myself&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So after the death of my teacher. and a few other things, I had some difficult times even meditating properly.  So I have been doing some major pufication on my holy guardian angel point.  I mean active magic, still can do.. spirit calls, no problem.  But really, Zen style meditation really tells you were you are at.   Simple meditation.  Object concentration on a single point, no thoughts, no distractions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At first, this was painful to even do.   Really painful after the grieving.   But I worked before now to get it up to a hardcore and honest 5 minutes.  I kinda feel into a everything is pointless loop after doing some of the funeral rights.. I was grieving pretty hard for a teacher.  Shit happens.  I will write more on this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;meditation-and-magical-work&quot;&gt;Meditation and Magical Work&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did the meditation outside, did Chilel for 20 minutes with 10 minutes of sitting still with object concentration.  If I was being fully honest,  it was 2 sets of 5  minutes of striaght object concentrations with no thinking.    I did the meditation and gigong outside ( 50 degree weather.   Will do a 3rd set of meditaiton.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the next couple days, will have a full plan down.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Domagick Day 1 Day 1, December 9, 2018</summary></entry></feed>