<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-01-03T16:34:36-05:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Do Magick For Andrieh Vitimus</title><subtitle>Andrieh doing the freaking magick.  Just that.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Post Challenge Insights and Talisman work</title><link href="/december-2018/2019/01/03/domagick-day-postchallenge-insigjts.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Post Challenge Insights and Talisman work" /><published>2019-01-03T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-03T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2019/01/03/domagick-day-postchallenge-insigjts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2019/01/03/domagick-day-postchallenge-insigjts.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/0a/e6/b7/0ae6b767e726b76527260162fcdcae0f.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rolling&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Post the challenge, I took a day off was a no-mag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are several things I took away from this challenge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;one&quot;&gt;One&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have to admit I am way overburdened, so much so that there was more then a few warning signals even with what was going on in the house before the death of my mentor and other deaths.   Death is never going to be easy, but I was at best tolerating stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;second&quot;&gt;Second&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heavy clearing work as much as I did, generates resentment which also has to be cleared.  I am doing alot more of the housework now, and using that as a meditation, see 4th way stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;third&quot;&gt;Third&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Things are not bothering me nearly as much which is huge progress, but I there are still attempts to violate boundaries.  Just a lot less and more manageable.  This tells me that like going down to point 4, I still have some issues on this point to correct.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;four&quot;&gt;Four&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Conceptualizing the overwhelming external anxiety as an external entity and throwing down as if it was a real spiritual attack did work, but clearly I haven’t won yet.  Its probably not possible to win actually.  Probably at best you can do is one step in front of the other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;five&quot;&gt;Five&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I let alot of things slide to do the cleansing work and have been in this under-seige mindset.  I went from grieving to intense cleaning.  Given point 4, not sure I can really work on more aspirational goals but I can take one day at a time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;six&quot;&gt;Six&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I probably have to admit, I don’t really like teaching computer science or more correctly, I dont want to spend all my time preparing and the curriculum is WAY WAY limited.  I am going to try to apply for side hustles at real colleges thinking that might be the ticket actually instead of the boot camp model, which I don’t really like and does not really give me much flexibility at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;seven&quot;&gt;Seven&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A big part of the pain point I was meditating on was the social bullshit I had to deal with.  I have been working on my MBA so I let a lot of things go in the public author thing.  People I thought I was cool with, well I got thrown away as garbage.  Actually it kinda hurt my feelings. 
I will be correcting this with both magic and content production, and I will be following my more “Chicago” Rules, as I mean No Quarter will be given and back to pretty aggressive magic for the witch craft of the mouth. Literally, looking back at the reading for a year, I totally thought this SHOULD be the course of action.  Magical Brass Knuckles and doing shit. I miss doing public rituals in that I love the real artistry of it, but I don’t miss conventions too much.  I do like smaller conventions, but I am just not a big partier or ass kisser, yep no.   The performance and the magick.. that that I love much.  Now I just wish I could get a few hundred dollars for costuming and props for each ritual so I could make them SUPER awesome pretty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;current-projects-and-aspirations&quot;&gt;Current projects and Aspirations&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Back to real body alchemy work, despite the time fuckery I put myself into.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Well, I got my Gym membership back.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Gonna try to get up at but fuck early, and go work out in the morning, we will see about that.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Got an armband thing for my phone, so I could do tai chi, serious walking, indoor biking.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Going to seriously be anal about my fitness pal and journaling this.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I am not sleeping like I should.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;It does not fell like this is anxiety, just like frustration that I couldn’t actually get a real vacation cause of the amount of cleansing work I did.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I really do not like mornings naturally at all, but I could do some solar sun rise shit that maybe will make it more interesting.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I am going to reclaim a working office/working space, but I would love to recreate what I call my dark temple don’t know how to do that one with the space, but I have some ideas.  I have the space have to con people into helping me move… I predict that will happen in may… yep that busy.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 30 New Years Day and New Methods</title><link href="/december-2018/2019/01/01/domagick-day-30-Bringing-new-Spirits-in.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 30 New Years Day and New Methods" /><published>2019-01-01T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-01T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2019/01/01/domagick-day-30-Bringing-new-Spirits-in</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2019/01/01/domagick-day-30-Bringing-new-Spirits-in.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/krishna.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Krishna&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;new-year-new-methods&quot;&gt;New Year New Methods&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First I did Qigong with a full Chilel set, then I did a full mantra work to evocation to the god Krishna.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Krishna is usually described as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Krishna (/ˈkrɪʃnə/,[8] Sanskrit pronunciation: [ˈkr̩ʂɳə]; Sanskrit: कृष्ण, translit. Kṛṣṇa) is a major deity in Hinduism. He is worshipped as the eighth avatar of the god Vishnu and also as the supreme God in his own right.[9] He is the god of compassion, tenderness, and love in Hinduism,[1][2] and is one of the most popular and widely revered among Indian divinities.[10] Krishna’s birthday is celebrated every year by Hindus on Janmashtami according to the lunisolar Hindu calendar, which falls in late August or early September of the Gregorian calendar.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working with this deity is purposefully working with an anathema for me.  This type of deity is not my cup of tea for alot of reasons, but when shit ain’t working do something different.  I did this work Zac Lui.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I got slightly more then I bargained for, and came to some heretical conclusions about the Krishna based on my verified personal gnosis. Zac got the same impressions without a direct conversation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can say the insights I got would make it very easy to work with at least Krishna and Laxmi with much greater success.  Now granted even Crowley sainted Krishna, I can tell you there is a strong connection to Krishna to the occult and various “occulty” people like Mathers, and the theosophists are all in on the Krishna.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are lots of big clues that Krishna is very tied to the archetype of the magician and part of that ( not all), is the extensive use of glamour and illusion.   The energy is such that the next day I had alot of trouble waking from the dream state and that is a BIG clue on the actual nature of the energy. Although interpreting the energy, I might have become even more cynical about religion and the religious side of occultism as theosophists and even Crowley fell into.   That said, I am pretty freaking relaxed today the day after, and care free.  That’s good and bad, probably on the whole really good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So all that means .. I got through the 30 days of body talisman and purification work ( KRISHNA totally fits into this if you read his mythology).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 29 New Years Eve Purification and Reading</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/31/domagick-day-29-More-Faery-Purification-end-of-year-reading.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 29 New Years Eve Purification and Reading" /><published>2018-12-31T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-31T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/31/domagick-day-29-More-Faery-Purification-end-of-year-reading</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/31/domagick-day-29-More-Faery-Purification-end-of-year-reading.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/0a/e6/b7/0ae6b767e726b76527260162fcdcae0f.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;legba&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I did the faery purification work with Jason Cowell in the forest.  This was pre-ritual ritual purification and protection ritual on our house.  This was a good 30 minutes of pretty intense work that really used faery tools I have developed to purify and cleanse.  There’s no link to share on those, as they are all mine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had gotten very weird effects.  The clouds started moving in a way Jason described as Children of the Corn.   They started to spiral too at times.  Also the forest got unbelievably still and there was a noticable temperature drop&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Midnight, I did a multi-hour possession ritual with Papa Legba to do the reading for the year.  Which I got, nope its only for people in our “house” not for the public.. but I would say it will be an interesting year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keep doing your magic, magic becomes more powerful when social reality breaks down.   It does not take a reading to see that social realities are breaking in the US, but the reading confirmed that. That means if you actually do the goddamn magic, your results may be better then expected.  You can actually pull ahead while most are drowning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are an insta-gram witch that utilizes the lifestyle accessory, eh, good luck.  Might be a good time to pick up &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Hands-Chaos-Magic-Reality-Manipulation/dp/0738715085/ref=tmm_pap_swatch_0?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1546450760&amp;amp;sr=8-1&quot;&gt;Hands-On Chaos Magic&lt;/a&gt; and do some magic.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 28 Back to Shiva</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/30/domagick-day-28-shiva-throwdown.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 28 Back to Shiva" /><published>2018-12-30T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-30T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/30/domagick-day-28-shiva-throwdown</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/30/domagick-day-28-shiva-throwdown.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://hindutsav1-codefear.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/08/lord-shiva.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Shiva&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;back-to-the-beginning-sorta&quot;&gt;Back to the Beginning Sorta&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was do these #domagick Challenges and get to day 28 and there is a bigger sort of climax.   Almost always, the last 2 days are somewhat anti-climatic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I did a multi-hour ritual to transform and extend the purification.  Shiva is the destroyer, and definitely the destroyer of problems too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It turns out the people living in our space that abruptly left after the major angel work, left some unfortunate negatively energy embed items in our house that also happened to be likely bloodied.  I don’t know why you’d think it was a good idea to leave anything with blood on it with a talented sorcerer, but these people where not thinking clearly.  I am not entirely sure this was a intentional spell, but it certainly was a negative talisman.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;om-namah-shiva-in-fire&quot;&gt;Om Namah Shiva in fire&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did a modified Fire Puja with a bonfire.  You can get the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.magical30.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/FireHoma.pdf&quot;&gt;simplified fire puja I do&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First I started the fire up in the traditional way.  Coconut and Ghee with Camphor.  I did well over 2 mala ( 108) of Ganesh mantras.   Consciously building up the fire with energy.   I kept going until the fire was really built.   Then at that point I switched to Shiva.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even building the fire up in a sanctified fashion, I felt there was a lot of baleful spirits present creating distractions.  You know the spirit in the corner of the eye situation.  It was annoying, but I kept going.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had also prepared logs with my negativity and others made logs too.  Zac Lui was present.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started places the additional logs and the fire got really freaking hot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This takes some concentration to do the mantra work and actually have some magick working while building the fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the fire was really going and it was clear Shiva was present, I put the entropic and bloodied talismans into the fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shit got UNBELIEVABLY Hot,  I mean what the fuck hot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the best way to think of this fire, and really what I kept seeing and feeling was the cremation grounds in India.  That I was burning the skulls and bodies of the issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://n3.sdlcdn.com/imgs/a/u/0/Freecultr-Express-Impressive-Black-Blue-SDL277602867-3-572ab.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Shiva in the dark&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;where-are-we-shiva&quot;&gt;Where Are We Shiva&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the fire has built and going.   Everything went black.   I could see the outlines of Shiva, right near me.  This was not ehem, a visualization.  I could close my eyes and see him dancing in the fire, easily.   No, this was with eyes open.  I kept doing the mantras till the other bloodied wood talismans and wood logs were unrecognizable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah, this was a long as ritual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I felt like this was a type of death or the void.   There was stillness.   I felt like Shiva definitely heard what I needed.  Transmute the bad into good, but I think, he took a look at a more.  The Hindu spirits get results, but they do it gently I found.  Coaxing you to move forward internally, and making the external elements show you are on the right path.   The Hebrew Angels are kinda dicks and if you know how to ground them into the world can work quite fast ( BTW, most people don’t do this, they work the angels in a “mental” sphere ).  Sometimes you need dicks, like when people are leaving negative talismans in your home who are guests, but sometimes you need coaxing.  I need coaxing now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Writing this, I am almost crying.  Its was a very sublime experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By this point, the annoyances of other spirits were gone and no longer preventing the work. You’d expect that when Lord Ganesha  and Lord Shiva go to town.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As this was a greater purification, I counted this as Qigong and meditation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/JfP8qPX.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Existential Dead&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;not-really-ok-after-it&quot;&gt;Not Really Ok After it.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was really not ok after this ritual.  I will be honest.   I tried to eat ( with poor food, fuck xmas food), but still was not really ok.  I just tried to get the “Void” out of my head, but struggled.  Spiritual people might be, totes dude, but really I couldn’t sit to do computer science work for my class.  After sleeping for 3 hours, I was ok.  Think about it like existential Chapel Perilous type moment.   Really great for growth on spiritual progression.  Really bad when you are totally time screwed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;still-in-a-fight-though&quot;&gt;Still in a Fight though.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shiva is very write, I need to be coaxed now.  I am still in a fight with the greater conceptuality of an malignant anxiety entity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I played video games, I played too late to get the void out of my head.  This was a trigger for other people’s self-esteem and anxiety issues which did clean up faster.  There are other self-issues that are getting to me regarding space, clearly some of the underlying issues come from previous trauma of the courts, but the fact I clearly can see the reaction and clearly can feel the process and have clear understanding of the why allows me to use some SWISH nlp patterns to deconstruct them.  Doing that bro, I am doing.  Some other issues with space and visitors, I am not sure how to address.   These issues are not important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is important however, is that each day I am doing one thing, one step to move foward&lt;/strong&gt;   Ultimately, that is best thing anyone can do regardless of whatever the situation is.  Don’t let the slick marketing of any other authors actually put you off.  There shit is there, despite the illusion.  Everyone has these very human problems, what is important is that you do something about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Change yourself or work to change the world, really both change the world.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-coding-aspect-of-this-challenge-fell-apart&quot;&gt;The Coding Aspect of this Challenge fell apart&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well I was able code the Markdown, and I like that.. but did not one fucking thing on theming work or actual coding.  Let me admit it, I dont like doing it much.   That “code for fun thing”, it ain’t me.   Time to get my management on real fast and work on that front.  Maybe there is some reclaiming of this, after all the purification&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 27 Re-access</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/29/domagick-day-27-Reasscessing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 27 Re-access" /><published>2018-12-29T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-29T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/29/domagick-day-27-Reasscessing</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/29/domagick-day-27-Reasscessing.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.esotericmeanings.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/thoth1_towertarotcard.jpg.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;tower&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;# Tower Card&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A couple days ago, I did a reading and the tower card kept coming out.   Obviously if you read this blog through, that happened.   The tower is not needfully always bad.   Just implies sudden change.   That definitely happened.  Now I have to re-access things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am definitely doing better as far as my emotional state, definitely more strong after the death of my mentor but there is a lot to think about that I have some room to think about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;todays-work&quot;&gt;Today’s Work.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I did 20 minutes of Microcosmic Orbit in a very NeiGong fashion.   Additionally I did some divinations to just check myself before I wrecked myself.   I am going to do some cleaning work ( physically re-organizing space).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;problem-my-eating-has-tanked&quot;&gt;Problem: My Eating has tanked&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the drama and the grieving, I have reverted to some bad habits around food given the stress of the death and bat shit crazy people in my home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;solution-proposed&quot;&gt;Solution Proposed&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting with the my fitness pal app again.  That should shame me enough to get it to work.
This isn’t going to help with the exercise point, that I have to seriously think about how with teaching the classes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;problem-doing-the-magic-has-actually-hurt-other-aspects-of-time&quot;&gt;Problem: Doing the magic has actually hurt other aspects of time&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have done some big lifting but that takes enormous time.  I am well behind on what I need to do for my classes, let alone what I would like to do in my metaphysical teachings.   Going to have to a bunch of cutting.   I mean this was just qigong and then morphed into some major heavy lifting rituals.   That wont be sustainable once classes start again for me&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;solution-&quot;&gt;Solution ???&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No good ones.
Yeah I don’t have a good one for this.  Time management starts to not work when you are overcommitted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;biking&quot;&gt;Biking?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hahahaah it got cold, but seriously, I need to get on the training, but the time is really hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know I a was seriously overburdened before the death, and then the stupid drama.   I probably needed to do the serious cleansing magic to even get to where I could think about the problems and take action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;other-issues&quot;&gt;Other issues&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just cause I got a victory on the anxiety front in the house, although not through the means I wanted but really people were seriously contemplating suicide in the home I own.  They should have been in a hospital, but they would not allow that.  They all needed to go.   Really I was just trying to do Angel work to really spiritually clean the house to give me some space to breath.   There are still issues challenges, and I think that fight with the conceptualization of anxiety as a malignant entity directly attacking is far from over.  At least I have some space to breath as I am coasting into the end of the magical 30.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"># Tower Card</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 26 More Crazy and Purification</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/28/domagick-day-26-more-shit-and-purification.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 26 More Crazy and Purification" /><published>2018-12-28T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-28T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/28/domagick-day-26-more-shit-and-purification</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/28/domagick-day-26-more-shit-and-purification.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.glc.org/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/glc-aboutthelakes-images-erie-large.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lake Erie&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So there was more full fuckery when people were moving today.  Left some nice little curse work behind around by the people leaving.  Realize we didn’t charge them rent.  Fun Times. Endless drama.   Really negative energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So first, I took all the negative vibes, curses and etc and dissolved them in a purification ceremony at the lake.  Dissolving ceremony to pull and capture the negativity and dissolve it in the lake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, I went and cleaned the two rooms with extreme cleansing magic.  There was some complications and it took a lot of energy, but I got everything cleared and did the clearing a few ways.   Made sure everything was cleared and threw away the remaining stuff the people left behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were still hiccups, and you could tell some of the things left behind negatively interfered with some of the people.   Cleared out all the shit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doing the purification rituals inlui of Qigong.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 25 The Shit-wave finally Breaks</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/27/domagic-day-25-Oh-Shit-Social-Breakdown-Resolved.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 25 The Shit-wave finally Breaks" /><published>2018-12-27T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-27T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/27/domagic-day-25-Oh-Shit-Social-Breakdown-Resolved</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/27/domagic-day-25-Oh-Shit-Social-Breakdown-Resolved.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://graduway.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/Good-Bye.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;goodbye&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So a big drain on the positive energy of our household was removed.  We had let some people stay to try to get their life together.   They are gone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They honestly created problems and did so in passive aggressive ways from breaking my space down ( and then playing the victim card after repeated requests to please don’t do that), refusing to energy cleanse themselves, or take any personal responsibility.  Many times they would pass it off like, oh its not us, its the disease but this is just gaslighting and they would ramp that fear and anxiety up in themselves to cause problems throughout the house.  I am very willing to help people but not people who won’t help themselves.   When you push boundaries to cause other people pain, you can’t really claim its just the mental illness sorry, not sorry.  Then they did this over text and honestly the most insulting way possible.   When they actually came, decided to be total assholes to their sponsor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is not how you gain control over your own life without major problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe this is a direct result of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/19/domagick-day-17-Changing-the-dynamic.html&quot;&gt;Angelic purification ritual&lt;/a&gt; based to purify and expel the negative energies in the house ( part of they were causing, part of it was our own issues, part of it was the reaction to those issues).  My intention was not to get rid of them, the intention was to clean up the negativity in the house and try to move everyone forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I did the Qigong and started to reinforce the angel work again to clean up the mess.  They were not able to get the stuff out fully so I expect drama tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The thing is I know there is still problems in the house, but it is less of the anxiety problems and less of the suicidal issues from others bringing real bad shit into the house.   I mean my fight with that &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/19/domagick-day-17-Changing-the-dynamic.html&quot;&gt;anxiety conceptualization&lt;/a&gt;, I can’t fight 5 on 1 with that.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 24 Client Work and More Cleansing</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/26/domagick-day-26-Client-work-and-lots-of-Qigong.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 24 Client Work and More Cleansing" /><published>2018-12-26T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-26T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/26/domagick-day-26-Client-work-and-lots-of-Qigong</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/26/domagick-day-26-Client-work-and-lots-of-Qigong.html">&lt;p&gt;I had to do some Paimon Work which involved creating a talisman to change their influence levels.  I can’t say exactly what was done, but this work was to demonstrate how to do extended drawing or scroll magic.   Yep no pictures again, client work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also re-asserted the angelic purification for the house and doing some Qigong work ( full Chilel set).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I had to do some Paimon Work which involved creating a talisman to change their influence levels. I can’t say exactly what was done, but this work was to demonstrate how to do extended drawing or scroll magic. Yep no pictures again, client work.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 23 Xmas, no Jesus</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/25/domagick-day-23-The-Queen-of-The-West.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 23 Xmas, no Jesus" /><published>2018-12-25T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-25T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/25/domagick-day-23-The-Queen-of-The-West</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/25/domagick-day-23-The-Queen-of-The-West.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/2524/0922/products/Sku_06836_06837-Buddha-Board_99155b23-4173-493b-9f70-6748f02ba284_1200x1200.jpg?v=1516892768&quot; alt=&quot;Buddha Board&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tested Qigong with my student and did a good 30 minutes of macrocosmic orbit.   One of the gifts I recieved was a buddha board.  It turns out this is a unbelievable talisman for spirit work in general, and just kinda cool.    The buddha board actual uses clear water and disappears as you write.   So it has a temporary ink scroll effect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zac and I summoned:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Xi-Wang-Mu.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Xi-Wang-Mu&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;xi-wang-mu-西王母&quot;&gt;Xi Wang Mu 西王母&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;queen-mother-of-the-west&quot;&gt;Queen Mother of the West&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;devourer-of-men&quot;&gt;Devourer of Men&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;granter-of-life&quot;&gt;Granter of Life&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;teacher-of-the-immortals&quot;&gt;Teacher of the Immortals&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a spirit that was bothering me to make contact because Zac had previously made contact but it just didn’t go right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ritual was actually one of the few non-purification rituals I  have done in the last 20 days, although arguably it was empowering.  This spirit is complicated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This ritual was almost purely Shamanic aka just fucking do it, not much ritual, but there were some ritual components.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So first we sanctified the Buddha Board and the space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was pretty sure I understood the spirit from the initial contact the spirit had made with me.  Now, I had very few details about the spirit outside of the name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went into a shamanic trance and started drawing on the board.  The board only lasts a minute, so its phenomenal automatic drawing/writing tool for trance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What did I draw.  Foxes, mountains, even the description as a truly beautiful woman was all right on the money.   I described a spirit that has the keys to life and death and is somewhat detached and humorous about that.   Then started relaying message through the board ( writing them down) and they would disappear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zac did divinations.   Everything was very consistent with historical information of the older versions of Xi Wang Mu, not the newer salvationist narratives.  Then shit got personal, and we tried to do a working directly with channeled energies from the spirit and into the board.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me, this seemed to become a moving spell like a animation as I was drawing it, because the board itself fades, it allows for a sort of moving sigil, or series of temporary&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a very cool experience and meets a lot of where I need to be working right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Portable.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Minimalist.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Essentialist&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now honestly the board disappears too quickly for normal sigil work, or at least you’d have to repetitively draw it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were some issues where the medium ( ahem Zac) interrupted in the spell work.   SO, I had to teach my bro some things about that style of work :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that said,  It was actually a very life affirming ritual ( she has access to the peaches that the immortals eat to become Taoist immortals).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So really the talisman work her was to sanctify the buddha board.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 22 Angel purification launched</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/24/domagick-day-Angel-Throwdown-of-clearing-power.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 22  Angel purification launched" /><published>2018-12-24T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-24T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/24/domagick-day-Angel-Throwdown-of-clearing-power</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/24/domagick-day-Angel-Throwdown-of-clearing-power.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/6/68/Guido_Reni_031.jpg/1280px-Guido_Reni_031.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;St.Michael&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So to deal with the idea of the conceptualization of the anxiety disorder of others as a &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/19/domagick-day-17-Changing-the-dynamic.html&quot;&gt;greater spiritual evil&lt;/a&gt;, I decided to do a more poweful angelic summoning of seven planetary angels&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Saturn    =  Cassiel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jupiter   =   Tzadikiel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mars  =   Samael&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sun   =  Michael&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Venus =  Haniel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mercury =  Raphiel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Moon =  Gabriel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this is a longer ritual and involves blessing each set of herbs and candles with the planetary intelligence, and then elevating like a journey to the planetary archanglel after starting with a planetary gateway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;LBRP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Planetary gateway opening&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Planetary Inteligence ( drawn on candle) and repeated drawn over herbs per planet&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Planetary archangel per planet&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;After 7 planetary archangels are present, call Metatron.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the herbs were blessed, and the candles tied to the evoked angel.   Part of the herbs were used to make a floor wash, part was used to make mojo bags.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was done with drawings on the floor, to make the floor talismanic with the intention to clear all the negativity out of the house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The house was completely rocking and I saw respectible  changes in behavior right from the start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Powerful changes actually. Moving forward on this.  Two rooms of people who were staying with us were actually pretty horrible.  There were lots of problems with them from crossing boundaries, to causing problems purposely. No they didn’t pay rent and we were trying to pay it forward. Completely horrible. New rule, Ill pay it forward from the outside of my house on.  The Archangel Michel got really pissed about how toxic the energy was and cleared it out.  Actually I cried while doing the summoning.  These parties were gone for Xmas.
We asperged the house after boiling blessed herbs together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again major positive behavior changes in .   Good times.  The actual ritual was like 2 hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a couple huge negatives.   It has taken me an immense bit of time to undo and work through the negativity around me that I could see after starting to do the qigong.  This was time I needed to work on my course work at Trilogy for the computer science classes.  I also because of the collective effect of the holiday + negativity clearing have been eating wrongly again.  Yes things are getting better, but its taken a toil to move the dial with the Qigong and purifications.   I have to get a handle on all that.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>