<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-12-27T23:22:15-05:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Do Magick For Andrieh Vitimus</title><subtitle>Andrieh doing the freaking magick.  Just that.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Day 22 Angel purification launched</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/24/domagick-day-Angel-Throwdown-of-clearing-power.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 22  Angel purification launched" /><published>2018-12-24T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-24T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/24/domagick-day-Angel-Throwdown-of-clearing-power</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/24/domagick-day-Angel-Throwdown-of-clearing-power.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/6/68/Guido_Reni_031.jpg/1280px-Guido_Reni_031.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;St.Michael&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So to deal with the idea of the conceptualization of the anxiety disorder of others as a &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/19/domagick-day-17-Changing-the-dynamic.html&quot;&gt;greater spiritual evil&lt;/a&gt;, I decided to do a more poweful angelic summoning of seven planetary angels&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Saturn    =  Cassiel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jupiter   =   Tzadikiel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mars  =   Samael&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sun   =  Michael&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Venus =  Haniel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mercury =  Raphiel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Moon =  Gabriel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this is a longer ritual and involves blessing each set of herbs and candles with the planetary intelligence, and then elevating like a journey to the planetary archanglel after starting with a planetary gateway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;LBRP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Planetary gateway opening&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Planetary Inteligence ( drawn on candle) and repeated drawn over herbs per planet&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Planetary archangel per planet&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;After 7 planetary archangels are present, call Metatron.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the herbs were blessed, and the candles tied to the evoked angel.   Part of the herbs were used to make a floor wash, part was used to make mojo bags.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was done with drawings on the floor, to make the floor talismanic with the intention to clear all the negativity out of the house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The house was completely rocking and I saw respectible  changes in behavior right from the start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Powerful changes actually. Moving forward on this.  Two rooms of people who were staying with us were actually pretty horrible.  There were lots of problems with them from crossing boundaries, to causing purposely.  Completely horrible.   The Archangel Michel got really pissed about how toxic the energy was and cleared it out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again major positive behavior changes.   Good times.  The actual ritual was like 2 hours.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 20 Microcosmic Orbit and Testing</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/22/domagick-day-20-Switched-to-Microcosmic-orbit.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 20 Microcosmic Orbit and Testing" /><published>2018-12-22T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-22T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/22/domagick-day-20-Switched-to-Microcosmic-orbit</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/22/domagick-day-20-Switched-to-Microcosmic-orbit.html">&lt;p&gt;Today was an insanely busy day.   I had my friend Zac Lui, who is a Chinese medicine expert.  I had him test my progress rehabilitating my energy system after my teachers death.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this is day 20.   He was pretty clear, VERY good progress.   My Microcosmic orbit was strong tight and fast.  It impressed him.  I did this for a good 20 minutes after an LBRP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So he did a pretty through look, thats what he concluded.   Verification of progress.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Today was an insanely busy day. I had my friend Zac Lui, who is a Chinese medicine expert. I had him test my progress rehabilitating my energy system after my teachers death.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 20</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/21/domagick-day-21-Faery-purification-talisiman.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 20" /><published>2018-12-21T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-21T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/21/domagick-day-21-Faery-purification-talisiman</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/21/domagick-day-21-Faery-purification-talisiman.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/man-light-people-night-sunlight-morning-639426-pxhere.com.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;purification&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;go-hard-or-go-home&quot;&gt;Go Hard or Go home.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So on line with this do magick challenge, I performed a purification ritual, a much larger Faery Purification ritual with the goal of a creating a greater talisman resonate with a specific type of faery entity.   I will not say much more about this talisman but will say it took me a good 5-6 hours and that was in a DEEP shamanic state, I mean deep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nope, no pictures my friends.  No pictures of my talismans.  I got the talisman done, but its not quite as pretty yet and I need to build a makeshift forge to do this. This talisman is directly related to the post &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/19/domagick-day-17-Changing-the-dynamic.html&quot;&gt;fighting the anxiety demon around me&lt;/a&gt;.  It is purposely attuned to help fight that, and some other issues of a similar to spiritual strenghtening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More details, nope.  Yes they do more then that, but nope nope nope I am not saying.  6 hours of work, not trivial spirits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Noticeable effects, on certain targets.  Yep…  They are shy spirits, cant say more.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 19 Qigong Qigong and Angels</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/21/domagick-day-19-its-a-blur.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 19 Qigong Qigong and Angels" /><published>2018-12-21T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-21T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/21/domagick-day-19-its-a-blur</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/21/domagick-day-19-its-a-blur.html">&lt;p&gt;So on day 19,   I did some Michael and Haniel work respectively  ( Venus and the Sun) to start refocusing and detailing, and turning things around.  So this was a continuation of the expression of conceptualizing some of the issues as external entities from &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/18/domagick-day-18-Every-Day-1-Step.html&quot;&gt;previous days&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started by blessing some every day items, and doing some some Qigong to build energy before doing anything else.  Then rolled into the angel work on the points, carving out some&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, this combination definitely seemed to work although there was some push back it on some of this, but there was most certainly progress that was visual and tangible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very much so, very much so.   Some reactions, some pushback, but tangible progress.   The Qigong, helps to ground and build earthy based Qi before doing the more cerebral energy work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this conception of some of the issues as a foreign malefic agent gives me some tools that are working to make progress.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">So on day 19, I did some Michael and Haniel work respectively ( Venus and the Sun) to start refocusing and detailing, and turning things around. So this was a continuation of the expression of conceptualizing some of the issues as external entities from previous days.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 18 - Every Day 1 Step</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/20/domagick-day-18-Every-Day-1-Step.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 18 - Every Day 1 Step" /><published>2018-12-20T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-20T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/20/domagick-day-18-Every-Day-1-Step</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/20/domagick-day-18-Every-Day-1-Step.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://encrypted-tbn0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcTB7Vt7oA8oKr_rmam0kpD2d5V0YjSXubk3I2TVE94I9Ligg-Qs&quot; alt=&quot;fish organizing&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;one-change-per-day&quot;&gt;One Change per day.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After my longer &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/18/Changing-the-dynamic.html&quot;&gt;post yesterday&lt;/a&gt;,  I realized too, that I can’t just do Qigong outside where I am staying and it will get better.  This does not fix any of the causes.  I realize pretty outright, that any changes I might try to make will be seriously contested.  Re-framing the overwhelming anxiety as a malevolent and entropic force, allows me to direct my anger at that force, not the people.  This is a major shift in conceptualizing the problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I fully expect to get outright resistance, passive resistance, broken stuff and more emotional whiplash as I push forward, but conceptualizing the force in this way allows me to show compassion towards the people and yet stand my ground.  I know this will be difficult, but conceptualizing the people as under the influence of a powerful being, lets me absolve some of the inter personal issues involved and take magical action against that being and not the people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is almost always the track you have to take, if you are doing healing magic with anyone who identifies with the disease egregore but has tried to get healing.  Once you loose the detachment, loose the ability to conceptualize the disease or spirit as separate from the person, you are really actually losing the fight to make anything better in the situation.   Step back, get outside help for perspective.  Stupid fae spirits had to do that for me again.. hahah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is this a sleight of mind, you bet your ass it is.&lt;/strong&gt;   Sometimes a useful remapping is better then the truth which is largely a lie too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, I did make a request to change some components of the environment, I believe the request will help all parties.  I do not know if the request which was made in a very business yet positive way will go over well.  Remember, social unpredictability is part of the “conceptualization” of the powers of the spiritual  malignant opponent.  Unpredictability is a means to take power over the social reality, and it further creates a cycle of anxiety.   I would expect a fair amount of resistance and I have some alternative solutions if it becomes an issue, but I will be taking the one step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And thats the lesson.
Other peoples inner demons and pain will infect you and consume you, manifesting in totally different ways once they get inside you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to remember, you can only take and secure one step at a time when making things better.   Not all of those steps will be doable in the time frame you would like.  People will resist and fight for the status quo, sometimes with great vigilance.  Be stronger, more patience and kinder then the resistance of the pain.  Can’t do something one way, do it another.  Can’t change the physical reality because of the status quo, call on spirits to help clear some of the pain.  Try again.  Repeat.  Analysis.  Find the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh yeah,  I did the Qigong today, again outside ( over by my work) but I did get some coffee after.
Haha, Also did the object concentration ( later at night).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 17 - Insight to Changes, Changing the Dynamic</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/19/domagick-day-17-Changing-the-dynamic.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 17 - Insight to Changes, Changing the Dynamic" /><published>2018-12-19T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-19T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/19/domagick-day-17-Changing-the-dynamic</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/19/domagick-day-17-Changing-the-dynamic.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.incimages.com/uploaded_files/image/970x450/True_Grit_1725x810-PAN_19746.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;grit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;forcing-it-to-change&quot;&gt;Forcing it to Change.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So after yesterdays big old &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/18/Jettison-and-cut.html&quot;&gt;wtf post&lt;/a&gt;, I pretty well decided in meditation to make some small changes.  I suggested that yesterday, but as I thought about it, there were even more simple changes I could make.  For instance, &lt;em&gt;why the fuck am I doing Qigong in a place basically toxic&lt;/em&gt;.  I am not backing away from that conclusion.  An LBRP is not enough, did I forget all the shit I do, apparently I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When in doubt, go to the spirits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://3.bp.blogspot.com/-UpGbUtb-CxA/VzJHsxIBFHI/AAAAAAAAs_M/P8JwaWZJIuI8ykQ4ASlFZHFxGbnY-FyvQCHM/s1600/forest-night-amazing-wallpapers.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;forest&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok this is not the forest, but I went out to a consecrated forest at night.  It was supremely sublime and pretty.   Cold and next to a waterfall which is the perfect fucking answer to anxiety energy toxins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anxiety is in Chi terms is a  Yang concentration in overdrive in channels that should not be so overstimulated.   That in returns FUCKS the rest of the body energy system, cause its got to draw from somewhere.      So fuck it….  Cold Air at night is like the total opposite of that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I outright did some other things to really BOOST my qigong.   First, I called to Gran Bwa after Legba.  Then in my own way, I called the night spirits around me.  Yes the winter monster night spirits ( its not all that bad seriously. I did not have to ask for help but they did.   For the first time in a long time,  I felt truly a sense of joy and peace after doing the Qigong.   I felt the night spirits and the river spirits, and they pulled a-lot of shit out.   Plus that, it was not human energy I was getting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anxiety is a human energy construct.  Animals over time might have anxiety, but mostly its fear and it is not the same.   They recover from anxiety a lot faster because they do not think about the state of their anxiety which makes it amp up the energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier in the day, I was very aware of the sensation of anxiety at a Christmas Dinner.  This is not a situation I should have had that anxiety.  I know these people well.  Granted, I do not really like some of them, but it should not be anxiety producing.  Usually it is not, and that is not me.  I am currently around people that have both social anxiety and general anxiety disorder. People with an anxiety disorder, no offense if you have it (and I wish for healing if you do), do not act in socially predicable ways.  In fact, you never quite now what will produce a major meltdown.  If this is what you are around most of the time, you start looking at others and start thinking will this provoke a adverse reaction?  Which starts a bigger and downward spiral of anxiety in you.  Even with shielding, and re-framing, being around this too much creates anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, we should correctly label that anxiety as a malignant and entropic entity.  An entity itself, that does not wish to negotiate as it represents the worst instincts and brings us to our most reptilian self.  Noticing I am not saying the people who suffer from this terrible affliction are malignant.  While fear is redeemable ( to survive), anxiety is false fear that only serves to propagate itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This, my friends, stalkers (hahah), and readers is a very shaman thing to do.  Once you have conceptualized something this far,  you can start to fight it directly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-simple-things-i-am-going-to-do-from-here-in-the-start-of-the-fight&quot;&gt;The simple things I am going to do from here, in the start of the fight.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do Qigong in the goddamn forest unless it is too cold, try to do it earlier.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Whenever possible go to the spirits, for a purer contact until a formal and separate temple can be re-established (or at least a private space with strong aka locked boundaries)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Avoid un-needed contact with non-family members that have these sorts of issues.   Do not let this be normalized in your head.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Find clubs ( obviously if you are reading, not my current Toastmasters group ) or other groups that clearly do not normalize the state of hyper anxiety.  While I can, I am seriously thinking of joining the Masons for this reason.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Avoid any groups or collectives that normalize the acceptance of the victim mentality.  ( its ok to be hurting, its not ok to accept that you cant do anything about this shit)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Usually I would at this stage whip up something in my private space, but the anxiety issues others have brought forth have seriously and continuously challenged my dominion over some spaces.  Anxiety is a tricky beast too.  People will try to “help” you who have the issues, only to violate boundaries set down and then turn back as the victim, and hyper anxiety state when they beat themselves up over someone pushing back on the boundary. Remember, defined as a malignant entropic being, its number 1 goal is to cause and create more anxiety in the host as well as everyone around them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The goal of the anxiety pathogen, is to create the illusion you have no real volition or control over your life, so of course, crossing boundaries to challenge the dominion over a stated space, is an attempt by the entity itself to destroy volition of someone else so it can spread&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might not agree with conceptualizing this as a spirit, but it is at least a thought form that pings each other person.  In fact, I can see it spread and cause pain like waves in those around me.   If a thing can be conceptualized as a spirit, it can be exorcised or fought as a spirit.  Sometimes, giving form and conceptualization to something makes it stronger.   In this case, if you think about it, anxiety thrives by not be called out in this fashion.   Likewise, people will usually not admit they can DO things to stop this shit and will not let you challenge the anxiety as it has become a defining aspect of their identity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Literally, its what I have been doing for the last 19 days of the challenge.   Qigong, banishing, thinking, repeat to get over the rawness after my teacher died and challenge those reactions. Usually, I would be more resilient. I see now, I may have to employ more aggressive tactics in a spiritual throw-down.   I have some .. “private” techniques.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Better to fight, then the alternative which is simply more anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/findaway.png&quot; alt=&quot;fight yo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 16 - The Word of the Day - Jettison</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/18/domagick-day-16-Jettison-and-cut.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 16 - The Word of the Day - Jettison" /><published>2018-12-18T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-18T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/18/domagick-day-16-Jettison-and-cut</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/18/domagick-day-16-Jettison-and-cut.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/dontrun.png&quot; alt=&quot;danger&quot; /&gt;
sh
Jettison.  The message from the universe.  The toastmaster word of the day.  Apropos exact message from the universe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Jettison 
	to throw away or get rid of something that is not wanted or needed
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 days of emotional turmoil basically caused by other people and my reaction to their reactions. I am partially to blame and I’ll own it.  Some of my decisions led to the place I am at.  Sometimes, it can’t get better till you clear out the poison and just admit, you fucked up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me be really blunt with the Qigong and other stuff I am doing, I can see my living conditions and lifestyle is not at all emotionally safe. Quite the opposite. I don’t have a safe space, and have stopped trusting my support network. I turn around and if I don’t get it from one angle I am getting it from another from the people around me.  Again, as the Shiva work all suggested, its social poisons dragging a lot of me down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of this, is kinda just too many people living in the same area,  some of it is not. There is simply a lot of emotions, that are not expressible even in what should be my space.  Its all really killing me one encounter at a time, and somedays I feel like I am losing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The energy work is keeping that from happening, and allowing me to &lt;strong&gt;detach as much as possible&lt;/strong&gt;. What the energy work is revealing, is the reality so I can do something about it.  Theres not much renewing going on, but at least I am getting some ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I have to find and seek out the wins, allow the garbage to dissolve in the eye of Shiva, and keep moving forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suffice to say, the drama continued from yesterday and when I did what was actually asked of me by others, I made it worse because they didn’t really mean it and then I had already done what was asked.   It made things worse of course. Vaguepost aside, and sorry about that…  I need to get back to trusting my intuition and being even more stubborn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Toastmasters too, I was further reminded some shit needs to change.  I  literally told people I was going to bring plates and did it in the google sheets.  Someone brought plates and stuff and they wanted just to make sure it was done.  I was done with that group, right there.   Tired of being disrespected. Really tired.  Jettison is the word of the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honestly, I feel like more and more, I probably after the death of my family member, I am in that realm of highly functioning depressed.  I am not sure it is really chemical, but it feels like every day, I have to deal with something insanely emotionally charged, that is extraordinarily draining to me. I cant shake it or get the space to shake it.   Like I said, physically speaking, my living situation is not emotionally safe for me. I kinda only have myself to blame for that based on a host of decisions, and because of that I cant get my footing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can admit today, after the meditation and work that truth about the emotional insecurity.  Before I was in denial.  Denial is not really a place where you can make change.  At least now, I can start using Qigong and reframing to toughen myself up, and reframe and rebuild.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All that is to say, what do I do about it?   Right now, I have some pretty good ideas.  Energy is the problem but I am going to have some time without work which means I can do larger rituals.   The first thing I will do is a much bigger and aggressive uncrossing with the archangel Micheal. There is other spirits I can work with and will try some of that too. Then keep doing the Qigong and a 1080 fire homa ( probably more of a bonfire) with Shiva… again truly forcing the negative energy to alchemize one way or another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So today, yes I did the Qigong today and LBRP, but I did it in my office at work.  Honestly, right now, despite all the bullshit at work, it feels more emotionally safe.  I did meditatively walk as well, and did 20 minutes of object concentration.  That’s why I can write about it, with some honestly and detachment.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">sh Jettison. The message from the universe. The toastmaster word of the day. Apropos exact message from the universe.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 15 - Anger Detoxing and Deconstructing</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/17/domagick-day-15-Anger-detoxing-deconstructing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 15 - Anger Detoxing and Deconstructing" /><published>2018-12-17T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-17T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/17/domagick-day-15-Anger-detoxing-deconstructing</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/17/domagick-day-15-Anger-detoxing-deconstructing.html">&lt;p&gt;Took 2 long walks.
Got to ride a train ( el ) which I did the sitting meditation.  I did the Qigong and angel work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At night, some people had moved stuff on me, and I got real angry.  Feeling of trapped and no respect.  There is alot of frustration over this, I know the real real reason was that I felt like I had no control.  Its the sensation of the walls closing in, and people giving you no space to recover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its been a rough couple days with this.  One fight, then another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In all seriousness, I really miss the meditative train rides.  Writing the blog posts a day or later removes much of the viciousness of the experience, so it less raw after a day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A sure sign, the banishing and Qigong is working as is the banishing rituals.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Took 2 long walks. Got to ride a train ( el ) which I did the sitting meditation. I did the Qigong and angel work.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 14 - Insight and Struggle</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/17/domagick-day-14-Struggling-with-a-few-things.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 14 - Insight and Struggle" /><published>2018-12-17T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-17T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/17/domagick-day-14-Struggling-with-a-few-things</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/17/domagick-day-14-Struggling-with-a-few-things.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.safetysign.com/images/source/large-images/G3540.png&quot; alt=&quot;Posion&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I could lie and saying it was a carefree Sunday, but it wasn’t.  Lot’s of drama, some of which was my fault.  I will admit that. Lots of times, I have to admit, I do not react well to anxiety and the feeling of being attacked.   I react very poorly.  Things got out of control. Conflict yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fight, Recovery.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sid the meditation.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Did the qigong under inside the LBRP.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Did actually take a longer walk.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Things sorta turned around in the day, but there was alot of issues that had nothing to do with me.   I had a couple days where I did not have to spend every minute studying for class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didn’t have time to fill this out when I should have.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 13 - Just doing the work and then Talisman</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/15/domagick-day-13-Crazy-Town-Classes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 13 - Just doing the work and then Talisman" /><published>2018-12-15T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-15T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/15/domagick-day-13-Crazy-Town-Classes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/15/domagick-day-13-Crazy-Town-Classes.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/71zcZ44eoDL._SX679_.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;shelf&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a day that I actually had to build a talisman, accidently.  Not just Qigong. So this one has a story.  I did the Qigong and the LBRP, although seriousy thinking of adding middle pillar work to my work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did do the Qigong and meditation work, although I am struggling with the object concentration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This talisman has an interesting story though.   So I was putting together a night stand shelf.  It is that one I put up that first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So at first, I was building the shelf, no issues.  Then I tried to add a couple hooks in, and bamo…   When screwing the hook in, the small brass hook literally twisted in half.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah so about that.  So the part of metal sticking out from the shelf was sharp.   I went downstairs and started working on this with the dremal…  Who was there.???&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Legba.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Legba&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Papa Legba, and he had things to say.  I was instructed to take items from his altar and decorate the shelf, to dress the entire shelf with Van Van oil, and bless it with both florida water and some frankensense which I did.   Then I put the pieces together, and there was some dicussions about that, where he was fucking with me and what incredients to put on there… but eventually we came to what we were going to do… He was just trying to be fun and playful, trying to get me to lighten up.  Point totally taken and totally correct.  I have too much to do and shit ain’t fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now to Papa’s credit, I was going to put my dream journal on this along with my tablet and phone, but I was shown images of just doing some simple minimalistic candle spells just with this 5” shelf next to a chair.  Dream candle work,  I could double wall the candle, and then glue the candle holder to a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.originalbotanica.com/7-day-silver-candle-holder/&quot;&gt;five inch base&lt;/a&gt; (which I promptly found on Original Products hahah, he was not kidding).  Dream candle work is interesting, here is the basic skinny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;so-here-is-a-gross-simplification-of-candle-dream-magic&quot;&gt;So here is a gross simplification of candle dream magic.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Banish or start with a cleansing bath.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Decorate candle appropriately&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Re-read Andrieh’s unpublished fire magic book or tell him to finish it (hahahaha).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dress candle and meditate with it, if sigil activate it.  Work with this in a relaxation to focus way.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lay in bed ( after activating), meditate to sleep with the candle.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Banish when you wake.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could write a whole book on this, but thats the basic skinny.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>