<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-12-24T22:55:14-05:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Do Magick For Andrieh Vitimus</title><subtitle>Andrieh doing the freaking magick.  Just that.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Day 18 - Day 19 Qigong Qigong and Angels</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/20/domagick-day-19-its-a-blur.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 18 - Day 19 Qigong Qigong and Angels" /><published>2018-12-20T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-20T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/20/domagick-day-19-its-a-blur</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/20/domagick-day-19-its-a-blur.html">&lt;p&gt;So on day 18,   I did some Michael and Haniel work respectively  ( Venus and the Sun) to start refocusing and detailing, and turning things around.  So this was a continuation of the expression of conceptualizing some of the issues as external entities from &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/18/domagick-day-18-Every-Day-1-Step.html&quot;&gt;previous days&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started by blessing some every day items, and doing some some Qigong to build energy before doing anything else.  Then rolled into the angel work on the points, carving out some&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, this combination definitely seemed to work although there was some push back it on some of this, but there was most certainly progress that was visual and tangible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very much so, very much so.   Some reactions, some pushback, but tangible progress.   The Qigong, helps to ground and build earthy based Qi before doing the more cerebral energy work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this conception of some of the issues as a foreign malefic agent gives me some tools that are working to make progress.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">So on day 18, I did some Michael and Haniel work respectively ( Venus and the Sun) to start refocusing and detailing, and turning things around. So this was a continuation of the expression of conceptualizing some of the issues as external entities from previous days.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 17 - Insight to Changes, Changing the Dynamic</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/18/domagick-day-17-Changing-the-dynamic.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 17 - Insight to Changes, Changing the Dynamic" /><published>2018-12-18T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-18T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/18/domagick-day-17-Changing-the-dynamic</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/18/domagick-day-17-Changing-the-dynamic.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.incimages.com/uploaded_files/image/970x450/True_Grit_1725x810-PAN_19746.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;grit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;forcing-it-to-change&quot;&gt;Forcing it to Change.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So after yesterdays big old &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/18/Jettison-and-cut.html&quot;&gt;wtf post&lt;/a&gt;, I pretty well decided in meditation to make some small changes.  I suggested that yesterday, but as I thought about it, there were even more simple changes I could make.  For instance, &lt;em&gt;why the fuck am I doing Qigong in a place basically toxic&lt;/em&gt;.  I am not backing away from that conclusion.  An LBRP is not enough, did I forget all the shit I do, apparently I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When in doubt, go to the spirits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://3.bp.blogspot.com/-UpGbUtb-CxA/VzJHsxIBFHI/AAAAAAAAs_M/P8JwaWZJIuI8ykQ4ASlFZHFxGbnY-FyvQCHM/s1600/forest-night-amazing-wallpapers.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;forest&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok this is not the forest, but I went out to a consecrated forest at night.  It was supremely sublime and pretty.   Cold and next to a waterfall which is the perfect fucking answer to anxiety energy toxins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anxiety is in Chi terms is a  Yang concentration in overdrive in channels that should not be so overstimulated.   That in returns FUCKS the rest of the body energy system, cause its got to draw from somewhere.      So fuck it….  Cold Air at night is like the total opposite of that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I outright did some other things to really BOOST my qigong.   First, I called to Gran Bwa after Legba.  Then in my own way, I called the night spirits around me.  Yes the winter monster night spirits ( its not all that bad seriously. I did not have to ask for help but they did.   For the first time in a long time,  I felt truly a sense of joy and peace after doing the Qigong.   I felt the night spirits and the river spirits, and they pulled a-lot of shit out.   Plus that, it was not human energy I was getting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anxiety is a human energy construct.  Animals over time might have anxiety, but mostly its fear and it is not the same.   They recover from anxiety a lot faster because they do not think about the state of their anxiety which makes it amp up the energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier in the day, I was very aware of the sensation of anxiety at a Christmas Dinner.  This is not a situation I should have had that anxiety.  I know these people well.  Granted, I do not really like some of them, but it should not be anxiety producing.  Usually it is not, and that is not me.  I am currently around people that have both social anxiety and general anxiety disorder. People with an anxiety disorder, no offense if you have it (and I wish for healing if you do), do not act in socially predicable ways.  In fact, you never quite now what will produce a major meltdown.  If this is what you are around most of the time, you start looking at others and start thinking will this provoke a adverse reaction?  Which starts a bigger and downward spiral of anxiety in you.  Even with shielding, and re-framing, being around this too much creates anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, we should correctly label that anxiety as a malignant and entropic entity.  An entity itself, that does not wish to negotiate as it represents the worst instincts and brings us to our most reptilian self.  Noticing I am not saying the people who suffer from this terrible affliction are malignant.  While fear is redeemable ( to survive), anxiety is false fear that only serves to propagate itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This, my friends, stalkers (hahah), and readers is a very shaman thing to do.  Once you have conceptualized something this far,  you can start to fight it directly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-simple-things-i-am-going-to-do-from-here-in-the-start-of-the-fight&quot;&gt;The simple things I am going to do from here, in the start of the fight.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do Qigong in the goddamn forest unless it is too cold, try to do it earlier.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Whenever possible go to the spirits, for a purer contact until a formal and separate temple can be re-established (or at least a private space with strong aka locked boundaries)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Avoid un-needed contact with non-family members that have these sorts of issues.   Do not let this be normalized in your head.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Find clubs ( obviously if you are reading, not my current Toastmasters group ) or other groups that clearly do not normalize the state of hyper anxiety.  While I can, I am seriously thinking of joining the Masons for this reason.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Avoid any groups or collectives that normalize the acceptance of the victim mentality.  ( its ok to be hurting, its not ok to accept that you cant do anything about this shit)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Usually I would at this stage whip up something in my private space, but the anxiety issues others have brought forth have seriously and continuously challenged my dominion over some spaces.  Anxiety is a tricky beast too.  People will try to “help” you who have the issues, only to violate boundaries set down and then turn back as the victim, and hyper anxiety state when they beat themselves up over someone pushing back on the boundary. Remember, defined as a malignant entropic being, its number 1 goal is to cause and create more anxiety in the host as well as everyone around them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The goal of the anxiety pathogen, is to create the illusion you have no real volition or control over your life, so of course, crossing boundaries to challenge the dominion over a stated space, is an attempt by the entity itself to destroy volition of someone else so it can spread&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might not agree with conceptualizing this as a spirit, but it is at least a thought form that pings each other person.  In fact, I can see it spread and cause pain like waves in those around me.   If a thing can be conceptualized as a spirit, it can be exorcised or fought as a spirit.  Sometimes, giving form and conceptualization to something makes it stronger.   In this case, if you think about it, anxiety thrives by not be called out in this fashion.   Likewise, people will usually not admit they can DO things to stop this shit and will not let you challenge the anxiety as it has become a defining aspect of their identity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Literally, its what I have been doing for the last 19 days of the challenge.   Qigong, banishing, thinking, repeat to get over the rawness after my teacher died and challenge those reactions. Usually, I would be more resilient. I see now, I may have to employ more aggressive tactics in a spiritual throw-down.   I have some .. “private” techniques.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Better to fight, then the alternative which is simply more anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/findaway.png&quot; alt=&quot;fight yo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 16 - The Word of the Day - Jettison</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/18/domagick-day-16-Jettison-and-cut.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 16 - The Word of the Day - Jettison" /><published>2018-12-18T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-18T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/18/domagick-day-16-Jettison-and-cut</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/18/domagick-day-16-Jettison-and-cut.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/dontrun.png&quot; alt=&quot;danger&quot; /&gt;
sh
Jettison.  The message from the universe.  The toastmaster word of the day.  Apropos exact message from the universe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Jettison 
	to throw away or get rid of something that is not wanted or needed
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 days of emotional turmoil basically caused by other people and my reaction to their reactions. I am partially to blame and I’ll own it.  Some of my decisions led to the place I am at.  Sometimes, it can’t get better till you clear out the poison and just admit, you fucked up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me be really blunt with the Qigong and other stuff I am doing, I can see my living conditions and lifestyle is not at all emotionally safe. Quite the opposite. I don’t have a safe space, and have stopped trusting my support network. I turn around and if I don’t get it from one angle I am getting it from another from the people around me.  Again, as the Shiva work all suggested, its social poisons dragging a lot of me down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of this, is kinda just too many people living in the same area,  some of it is not. There is simply a lot of emotions, that are not expressible even in what should be my space.  Its all really killing me one encounter at a time, and somedays I feel like I am losing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The energy work is keeping that from happening, and allowing me to &lt;strong&gt;detach as much as possible&lt;/strong&gt;. What the energy work is revealing, is the reality so I can do something about it.  Theres not much renewing going on, but at least I am getting some ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I have to find and seek out the wins, allow the garbage to dissolve in the eye of Shiva, and keep moving forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suffice to say, the drama continued from yesterday and when I did what was actually asked of me by others, I made it worse because they didn’t really mean it and then I had already done what was asked.   It made things worse of course. Vaguepost aside, and sorry about that…  I need to get back to trusting my intuition and being even more stubborn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Toastmasters too, I was further reminded some shit needs to change.  I  literally told people I was going to bring plates and did it in the google sheets.  Someone brought plates and stuff and they wanted just to make sure it was done.  I was done with that group, right there.   Tired of being disrespected. Really tired.  Jettison is the word of the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honestly, I feel like more and more, I probably after the death of my family member, I am in that realm of highly functioning depressed.  I am not sure it is really chemical, but it feels like every day, I have to deal with something insanely emotionally charged, that is extraordinarily draining to me. I cant shake it or get the space to shake it.   Like I said, physically speaking, my living situation is not emotionally safe for me. I kinda only have myself to blame for that based on a host of decisions, and because of that I cant get my footing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can admit today, after the meditation and work that truth about the emotional insecurity.  Before I was in denial.  Denial is not really a place where you can make change.  At least now, I can start using Qigong and reframing to toughen myself up, and reframe and rebuild.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All that is to say, what do I do about it?   Right now, I have some pretty good ideas.  Energy is the problem but I am going to have some time without work which means I can do larger rituals.   The first thing I will do is a much bigger and aggressive uncrossing with the archangel Micheal. There is other spirits I can work with and will try some of that too. Then keep doing the Qigong and a 1080 fire homa ( probably more of a bonfire) with Shiva… again truly forcing the negative energy to alchemize one way or another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So today, yes I did the Qigong today and LBRP, but I did it in my office at work.  Honestly, right now, despite all the bullshit at work, it feels more emotionally safe.  I did meditatively walk as well, and did 20 minutes of object concentration.  That’s why I can write about it, with some honestly and detachment.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">sh Jettison. The message from the universe. The toastmaster word of the day. Apropos exact message from the universe.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 18 - Insight to Changes, Changing the Dynamic</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/18/domagick-day-18-Every-Day-1-Step.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 18 - Insight to Changes, Changing the Dynamic" /><published>2018-12-18T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-18T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/18/domagick-day-18-Every-Day-1-Step</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/18/domagick-day-18-Every-Day-1-Step.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://encrypted-tbn0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcTB7Vt7oA8oKr_rmam0kpD2d5V0YjSXubk3I2TVE94I9Ligg-Qs&quot; alt=&quot;fish organizing&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;one-change-per-day&quot;&gt;One Change per day.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After my longer &lt;a href=&quot;http://domagick.andriehvitimus.com/december-2018/2018/12/18/Changing-the-dynamic.html&quot;&gt;post yesterday&lt;/a&gt;,  I realized too, that I can’t just do Qigong outside where I am staying and it will get better.  This does not fix any of the causes.  I realize pretty outright, that any changes I might try to make will be seriously contested.  Re-framing the overwhelming anxiety as a malevolent and entropic force, allows me to direct my anger at that force, not the people.  This is a major shift in conceptualizing the problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I fully expect to get outright resistance, passive resistance, broken stuff and more emotional whiplash as I push forward, but conceptualizing the force in this way allows me to show compassion towards the people and yet stand my ground.  I know this will be difficult, but conceptualizing the people as under the influence of a powerful being, lets me absolve some of the inter personal issues involved and take magical action against that being and not the people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is almost always the track you have to take, if you are doing healing magic with anyone who identifies with the disease egregore but has tried to get healing.  Once you loose the detachment, loose the ability to conceptualize the disease or spirit as separate from the person, you are really actually losing the fight to make anything better in the situation.   Step back, get outside help for perspective.  Stupid fae spirits had to do that for me again.. hahah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is this a sleight of mind, you bet your ass it is.&lt;/strong&gt;   Sometimes a useful remapping is better then the truth which is largely a lie too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, I did make a request to change some components of the environment, I believe the request will help all parties.  I do not know if the request which was made in a very business yet positive way will go over well.  Remember, social unpredictability is part of the “conceptualization” of the powers of the spiritual  malignant opponent.  Unpredictability is a means to take power over the social reality, and it further creates a cycle of anxiety.   I would expect a fair amount of resistance and I have some alternative solutions if it becomes an issue, but I will be taking the one step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And thats the lesson.
Other peoples inner demons and pain will infect you and consume you, manifesting in totally different ways once they get inside you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to remember, you can only take and secure one step at a time when making things better.   Not all of those steps will be doable in the time frame you would like.  People will resist and fight for the status quo, sometimes with great vigilance.  Be stronger, more patience and kinder then the resistance of the pain.  Can’t do something one way, do it another.  Can’t change the physical reality because of the status quo, call on spirits to help clear some of the pain.  Try again.  Repeat.  Analysis.  Find the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh yeah,  I did the Qigong today, again outside ( over by my work) but I did get some coffee after.
Haha, Also did the object concentration ( later at night).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 14 - Insight and Struggle</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/17/domagick-day-14-Struggling-with-a-few-things.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 14 - Insight and Struggle" /><published>2018-12-17T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-17T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/17/domagick-day-14-Struggling-with-a-few-things</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/17/domagick-day-14-Struggling-with-a-few-things.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.safetysign.com/images/source/large-images/G3540.png&quot; alt=&quot;Posion&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I could lie and saying it was a carefree Sunday, but it wasn’t.  Lot’s of drama, some of which was my fault.  I will admit that. Lots of times, I have to admit, I do not react well to anxiety and the feeling of being attacked.   I react very poorly.  Things got out of control. Conflict yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fight, Recovery.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sid the meditation.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Did the qigong under inside the LBRP.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Did actually take a longer walk.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Things sorta turned around in the day, but there was alot of issues that had nothing to do with me.   I had a couple days where I did not have to spend every minute studying for class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didn’t have time to fill this out when I should have.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 15 - Anger Detoxing and Deconstructing</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/17/domagick-day-15-Anger-detoxing-deconstructing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 15 - Anger Detoxing and Deconstructing" /><published>2018-12-17T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-17T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/17/domagick-day-15-Anger-detoxing-deconstructing</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/17/domagick-day-15-Anger-detoxing-deconstructing.html">&lt;p&gt;Took 2 long walks.
Got to ride a train ( el ) which I did the sitting meditation.  I did the Qigong and angel work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At night, some people had moved stuff on me, and I got real angry.  Feeling of trapped and no respect.  There is alot of frustration over this, I know the real real reason was that I felt like I had no control.  Its the sensation of the walls closing in, and people giving you no space to recover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its been a rough couple days with this.  One fight, then another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In all seriousness, I really miss the meditative train rides.  Writing the blog posts a day or later removes much of the viciousness of the experience, so it less raw after a day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A sure sign, the banishing and Qigong is working as is the banishing rituals.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Took 2 long walks. Got to ride a train ( el ) which I did the sitting meditation. I did the Qigong and angel work.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 13 - Just doing the work and then Talisman</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/15/domagick-day-13-Crazy-Town-Classes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 13 - Just doing the work and then Talisman" /><published>2018-12-15T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-15T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/15/domagick-day-13-Crazy-Town-Classes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/15/domagick-day-13-Crazy-Town-Classes.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/71zcZ44eoDL._SX679_.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;shelf&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a day that I actually had to build a talisman, accidently.  Not just Qigong. So this one has a story.  I did the Qigong and the LBRP, although seriousy thinking of adding middle pillar work to my work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did do the Qigong and meditation work, although I am struggling with the object concentration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This talisman has an interesting story though.   So I was putting together a night stand shelf.  It is that one I put up that first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So at first, I was building the shelf, no issues.  Then I tried to add a couple hooks in, and bamo…   When screwing the hook in, the small brass hook literally twisted in half.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah so about that.  So the part of metal sticking out from the shelf was sharp.   I went downstairs and started working on this with the dremal…  Who was there.???&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Legba.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Legba&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Papa Legba, and he had things to say.  I was instructed to take items from his altar and decorate the shelf, to dress the entire shelf with Van Van oil, and bless it with both florida water and some frankensense which I did.   Then I put the pieces together, and there was some dicussions about that, where he was fucking with me and what incredients to put on there… but eventually we came to what we were going to do… He was just trying to be fun and playful, trying to get me to lighten up.  Point totally taken and totally correct.  I have too much to do and shit ain’t fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now to Papa’s credit, I was going to put my dream journal on this along with my tablet and phone, but I was shown images of just doing some simple minimalistic candle spells just with this 5” shelf next to a chair.  Dream candle work,  I could double wall the candle, and then glue the candle holder to a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.originalbotanica.com/7-day-silver-candle-holder/&quot;&gt;five inch base&lt;/a&gt; (which I promptly found on Original Products hahah, he was not kidding).  Dream candle work is interesting, here is the basic skinny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;so-here-is-a-gross-simplification-of-candle-dream-magic&quot;&gt;So here is a gross simplification of candle dream magic.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Banish or start with a cleansing bath.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Decorate candle appropriately&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Re-read Andrieh’s unpublished fire magic book or tell him to finish it (hahahaha).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dress candle and meditate with it, if sigil activate it.  Work with this in a relaxation to focus way.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lay in bed ( after activating), meditate to sleep with the candle.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Banish when you wake.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could write a whole book on this, but thats the basic skinny.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 12 - Christian Coaching, Apostello, Toastmasters, Changing Perspective</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/14/domagick-december-day-12-Christian-Coaching-Toastmasters-What-is-needed.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 12 - Christian Coaching, Apostello,  Toastmasters, Changing Perspective" /><published>2018-12-14T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-14T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/14/domagick-december-day-12-Christian-Coaching-Toastmasters-What-is-needed</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/14/domagick-december-day-12-Christian-Coaching-Toastmasters-What-is-needed.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.apa.org/images/body-stress-title-image_tcm7-230134.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Thinking&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;time-stress-change&quot;&gt;Time Stress Change&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All three things. I am going to be really honest, I am pretty stressed out but a few things.  Really thinking about it really to get down to business of self and reality change, a few things stand out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I shouldn’t have take the coding class on, but my logic was sound.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I should be really looking for a new job as well ( although well get to this in a second)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Yup, too many commitments, just a few.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;There are a few I can’t say even in the blog without repercussions, but I will say others people are making somethings worse ( and thats always the way).  You have to take one thing at a time, what is the piece you can make better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now earlier in this domagick challenge, I had mentioned that yes I was dealing with alot including &lt;a href=&quot;http://google.com&quot;&gt;Death&lt;/a&gt;, but I do not even have time to make code changes to the template, thats kinda of a fail on my part.   I can tell too because I am starting to get angry when other people’s demons interfere with timings.  Actually dealing with other meltdowns, pettiness, and shit is why I am probably so socially isolating myself.   I do not have the bandwidth for any bullshit.  I need to reign that in.  I will be blunt, I don’t deal with emotionally charged situations that I think are way off the mark as far as reactions go well.  I generally treat it as manipulation and in some cases you’d have a tough sell to convince me its not at least unconsious control techniques.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The flaw there is mine.  You cant change anyone ( ok well maybe you can with particularly potent binding magic), but at that point its not worth trying to kid yourself that its anything like a real “connection”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I need to embrace a serious level of involved yet Shiva like detachment with laser focus.  Hence the actual object concentration work.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That part of this challenge isn’t going so well, and that should really make sense based on what I am saying.  This is where we literally can start matching up the internal state to the social state and thus the energy state.   They all inter-relate.  Purposesly&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I knew I took the bootcamp coding on as a sort of strategic idea based on the results of a Lucifer summoning.   I had to take the chance for a different road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love teaching.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So teaching coding should make the process of coding eh, less problematic.   Truth is, while I can do it, its still a pain in the ass, and I really am over it.  I still hate the over the top puppy dog attitude of newer developers.  Sure I have mixed feelings, on learning new stuff, but it is stressful. I love learning stuff and working through it, but not at the timeframe I have to do it in.  I like the teaching, but have really mixed feelings on the subject.  Coding is tedious to me alot of the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Jury is out on whether or not its a good idea, but it was worth taking a shot.  I am learning about myself.  Sometimes, you have to try something to rule it out, since it looks on paper good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thought I could “make the coding better” by doing that .. and maybe it will when I dont have to teach and learn, but right now.. not so sure.   There was no real way to move forward without it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This relates to the body talisman and gigong work directly.   I have a lot of energy going out and if the things do not really bring joy or there isn’t really a strong motivation, the things are intensely draining, when I am struggling with … well energy.   Too many really unsatisfying interactions and activities and thats where you start looking at where to cut and doing something different else you get drained, and then sick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-toastmasters-problem&quot;&gt;The Toastmasters Problem&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am part of a Toastmaster group,  I am trying to better my public speaking.  I will be blunt, this year the toastmaster stuff is not going well.  I was “voted” in absentia as an officer and the group dynamics and group culture is horrible for me in a lot of ways.  I really am outsider, I don’t have time to work on the speeches, the group is terrible at logistics, and gives lip service to getting new people in, but really it very insular.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question I always want to ask, outside the endless group pressures, is why should I care about the Toastmaster merit badges.  I want to get better at speaking and speaking for profit, end stop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Desire for getting better at that speaking
Versus
The Reality of the vehicle not working&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How is this related to Qigong.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Glad you asked. Qigong is about pulling energy in and out, but the real goal is to stop the bleeding of unneeded energy loss.  To make life corrections based on the how the energy us coming in and out.   This is the little talked about spiritual effect of what should happen if you are meditating on the Qigong process.  You don’t have to work nearly as hard to replenish your energy if shit is working on the point of Joy and at least you are motivated to do some things.  If you have to force yourself to do anything, like go to work in the morning cause, you hate it… thats shit is draining chi fast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I should be motivated to make Toastmasters work.  I want to get supremely awesome at public speaking.   I am good, but not supremely awesome.  The endless group pressures, lack of value add, and nepotistic social merit badges are all seriously energy drains.  It gets in the way of the goal which DOES bring me energy, it makes the goal not possible, and it makes stuff odd.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, so is my frustration at not having the time to really work on the speeches with the correct time.&lt;br /&gt;
Taking together, this is actually why Qigong should not be considered so simple.  Reflecting on the energy loss accross multiple domains of life, and then trying to rebuild&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is why in westernized Qigong and Buddhism, everything revolves around the concept of being happy which is definately a kinda of sugar laden mc-Qigong of spiritual diabetes.  That and fear sells well.&lt;br /&gt;
Instead we still should be concentrating on meaning, and motivation in relation to what is bringing motivation ( which is a symptom of more energy, not the cause, but you can use Qigong to build motivation because the process goes both ways).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;pastoral-apostle-coaching-and-using-the-principle-of-thought&quot;&gt;Pastoral Apostle Coaching and Using the principle of Thought&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I met with this pretty hard co
re Christian coach who took is models for evangellical apostle missionary work and applied it to business.  Now, he had a pretty clear model and it would be very effective.   After the 5000 he was asking for in an intensive, and 400 a month for a coaching session.  Yeah that kinda of $$$.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I respected the dude.  I am probably not his best choice of customer as the Christinity would throw me off, but I still might bite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are several aspects of the system but most boil down to finding elements of joy and motivation, then setting expectations low enough to make progress.   A fine strategy.  What the system does though, kinda revealed another problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could do something exactly like this.  In fact, I might not sell it the way he did, but I could come up with a 4 element system that produces a 5 result .. ( ehem western elements yo).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The system basically uses a technique I learned in Design thinking.  Repeating a few things, like categorizing things to 3-7 things ( 5 in this case), then repeating&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See the flaw for a multi-dimensional thinker, all that shit is a pretty extreme and vulgar simplification of a system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pick 5 thinks in the past, present future of tools you like.
Use 4 areas of life, in careful categories, that sumarize all reality for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See the connection to McSpirituality and Mc-Answers.   This is actually what will sell.  I am not so concerned with the specifics of his system…. but what he put together.  I know I could do it and I do not, cause the Mc-Answers get to me.   Life is complicated, but all these systems simplify things too far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do they work, eh that is a maybe, but they have to help since they are focusing tools. So again, where does the issue lay…  If you thought I might say in me, you would be correct.  My need to think multi-dimensionally is an addition, a crutch.  Applying this to others and their needs, are pointless.  Its a need to be percieved as intelligent.  No doubt, a partial reaction to negative feedback from my first book which was accessible, but some ehem, jealous haters, trashed because it was not intellectually elitist enough.  Read that as anyone could understand it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I could use NLP, or I could find the energy tied to the mental construct, and use the GODDAMN Qigong.  I just have to keep doing it, starting from a clear space, think about that issue which should be nasty in feeling, and dissolve it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you got that, its a big hint how hypnosis, Qigong and cognitive science all interact together.   Like where that line is going, well I take much further in my &lt;a href=&quot;http://andriehvitimus.com/shapeshift&quot;&gt;shapeshifting course&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 11 - The Bad and the Worst</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/13/domagick-december-day-11-The-good-the-bad.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 11 - The Bad and the Worst" /><published>2018-12-13T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-13T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/13/domagick-december-day-11-The-good-the-bad</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/13/domagick-december-day-11-The-good-the-bad.html">&lt;p&gt;Yeah, talk about the obsticles.  Even the dog peed on the bed which created chaos, entropy, and lots of anxiety.  So many pain points, and all these downward spirals from that point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 am in texas right or a song goes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I only really had the time to banish with a LBRP, then straight object concentration (30 minutes).  I was amped up with the situation and trying to clean it so I did not do Gigong, just the focusing excercise ( anxiety being too much energy in general, and gigong would clear it out but would have also woke me up, at 3 am.. no dice.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was going to write a angry post but Im not.  I am just going to say I did something.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Yeah, talk about the obsticles. Even the dog peed on the bed which created chaos, entropy, and lots of anxiety. So many pain points, and all these downward spirals from that point.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 10 - Stressing and Bad Habits</title><link href="/december-2018/2018/12/12/domagick-day-10-december-talismons-bad-stressy-habit.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 10 - Stressing and Bad Habits" /><published>2018-12-12T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-12T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>/december-2018/2018/12/12/domagick-day-10-december-talismons-bad-stressy-habit</id><content type="html" xml:base="/december-2018/2018/12/12/domagick-day-10-december-talismons-bad-stressy-habit.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/eating-too-much-623x350.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;eating too much&quot; title=&quot;an image title&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somewhere along the day, I got an extra day in here.  Not lost a day, but really thought I had not done Gigong on a day I CLEARLY did, because I did ritual.. I am keeping track, but the few days of rituals, I know I did some gigong, and thought no.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sigh..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did the Gigong work inside a wrapped LBRP, but it was really hard and I will go into why.  And did a 20 minute stint of meditaiton as well as some divinations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;other-peoples-demons&quot;&gt;Other People’s Demons&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In our house, my office  has a lower ceiling.  It is in the basement.  So I have been trying to do the Gigong in our living room.   Generally, that means I have to wait till everyone goes to bed.   Today, everyone went to bed and I was setting up to use the living room and go forward, only the minute I was ready to start my step daughter decided she was not going to bed, plopped down, and turned on youtube videos on her cell phone even after I told her, she had went to bed and I was going to do gigong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was carelessly malicious, but not consciously so. In your own practice, any extended spiritual purification or alchemy will be met with resistance from other people. End Stop.  This is almost a truth.  The obsticles will always appear from other people.  Perhaps its the neighbor, perhaps its your stepdaughter, but obsticles will appear.   I recgonized it for what it is.  Generally speaking, other people are rarely going to be your ally in self change.  Our subconsious minds want to keep people in the similair boxes, automates that process, and that really often means preventing healing or growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not sure what the “motivation” was in this case, but I powered through the gigong and the angel work.  Even with noise canceling headphones, I could hear the videos playing. In part, it was probably a “how dare I”.   The living room is always a contensious area.  I kept going through it.  Now the natural reaction for me was of course anger.  I said I had needed the living room, it was ignored, and thats how the fuck you is.  This time, I kept doing the Gigong in front of the obsticle and powered through it so I could release more anger. In retrospect, the obsticle just shows the desire I have for a seperated temple space, but I know…  You need to be able to do the work anywhere, under any conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Obsticles, even from those you love, only really tell you, you are on the right track.  Maybe not thank them, but mentally thank them for telling you, you are on the right track as far as the general spiritual work you are doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An echo in the social realms to create an unrelated obsticle, is a sign of some actual progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;bad-habits-coming-out&quot;&gt;Bad Habits, Coming out&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah so, many people know I have struggled with some health weight issues.   This is pretty fucking common knowledge  ( please do not offer me advice on this point, seriously just don’t).   After the few days, of pretty hard core ritual, I can honestly say I ate like S-h-i-t the last couple days.  Not so much BIG MAC level of shit, but shit.  Too quick of food, not really up the speed I should be doing.  I know with the computer science teaching, I have really been struggling on this front too, slipping some times, but after the few rituals … yeah problems.  Super hungry&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The worst offending foods are&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Chicken Tenders ( when I am hungry at like 11 pm after class)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Peanut Butter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Chicken Wings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Non of that is exactly good. I am just always super hungry.  I am not sure what my body is trying to do, but clearly eating more isnt going to really build up any extra chi.   I have somewhat seen I could mitigate some of this with extremely spice food ( thats the wings and the Tenders).  Essentially, I take the tenders and make hot chicken, but I could easily do this with the breading and make healthy hot chicken.  At 11, I just noticed after working a full day and teaching classes, its a real struggle.   I wanted to try to get lunch excercise in, but I think I am seriously overestimating my energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;technical-issues&quot;&gt;Technical Issues&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well I tried to get the Tumblr API to work to cross post things I post here to Tumblr.  So that is me trying to work through the “coding as fun” idea.  Its not.  The tumblr API kinda sucks ass, and I need to move to a node.js or something system to do it, since I cannot just impliment it in my liquid straight html context.  SUCK.. thats a big blocker on that.  But I have to work the node nyway, but at least the content is all in markdown.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>