<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-12-07T18:51:12-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Do Magick For Andrieh Vitimus</title><subtitle>Andrieh doing the freaking magick.  Just that.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Day 4 - Domagic… just doing a movie</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/06/domagick-day-4-december.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 4 - Domagic... just doing a movie" /><published>2018-12-06T02:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-06T02:35:37-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/06/domagick-day-4-december</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/06/domagick-day-4-december.html">&lt;p&gt;
    Well the movie says it all right.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;https://andriehvitimus.cdn.vooplayer.com/assets/vooplayer.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;iframe allow=&quot;autoplay&quot; class=&quot;video-player-container vooplayer&quot; data-playerId=&quot;MTE1NTY3&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; style=&quot;max-width:100%&quot; name=&quot;vooplayerframe&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot; src=&quot;https://andriehvitimus.cdn.vooplayer.com/publish/MTE1NTY3&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Well the movie says it all right.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 3 - Domagic… not very exciting</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/05/domagick-day-3-december-3.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 3 - Domagic... not very exciting" /><published>2018-12-05T02:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-05T02:35:37-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/05/domagick-day-3-december-3</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/05/domagick-day-3-december-3.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;fed-the-spirits-and-did-the-work&quot;&gt;Fed the spirits and did the work.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well I fed the spirits, did the Gigong, meditated.
Was very very tired today… and its still 1 when I am starting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Probably not the most exciting magic, but alas at least I am trying.   I have been thinking I need to do alot more talismans to destroy… or linking items and embuing those items to clear things out.   I will add more later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did not fix the programming issues, so this is still broke ( at least in part )….   Keep on keeping on.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Fed the spirits and did the work. Well I fed the spirits, did the Gigong, meditated. Was very very tired today… and its still 1 when I am starting.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 2 - High Weidness today/Fire Alchemy!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/04/december-talismans-day-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 2 - High Weidness today/Fire Alchemy!" /><published>2018-12-04T02:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-04T02:35:37-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/04/december-talismans-day-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/04/december-talismans-day-2.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;day-2-high-weidness-today&quot;&gt;Day 2, High Weidness today.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/3/34/Camp_fire.jpg/1584px-Camp_fire.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fire&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;opted-for-a-big-fire-ritual&quot;&gt;Opted for a Big Fire Ritual&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In lieu of Qigong, I did a large fire ritual over several hours.
There was tremendous oddities on multiple aspects of the work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a release and dissolve ritual under Shiva, and roughly would be a homa (without the formality).  I had many old ritual remains and herbs and I had No fucking idea what they were for.  They were not labled.  So I through everything into a fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me say, I got some push back right away on many fronts including the weather, but let me say, no I wont be asking for permission to do anything I need to, as far as removing things that seem like life blocks and stagnent energy from herbal mixture/ritual remains that not only were unlabled but were definately feeling stagnent.  End Sto&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-fire-that-wasnt&quot;&gt;The Fire that wasn’t&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When weird shit happens, especially with fires, I pay attention.  I am tryting to write a book on this.  I could not, could not light the fire.  Not at all.  I tried and struggled with this for 2 hours chanting the Ganesh Mantra “Om Ganapataye Svaahaa”  after formally blessing the fire and even asking Agne for help.  Got it to smoke and thats that.  Now there was a lot of herbs in there and there was some other ritual remains.  I took this as real bad sign that shit was way more blocked up then it should have been.  I probably made the fire wrong too and I had decided to do this fire ritual instead of taking a bike ride ( Not sure I made the right decision).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I acknowledged, just that fuck.   I can’t even get the fire going, the obsticles must be much worse then I thought.  My energy was a little more stagnet and the shit I was trying to release EVEN worse then I thought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its just information, right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;then-the-oddity-occured&quot;&gt;Then The oddity occured.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So the fire was fucking out.  I mean fucking out.  Sure it was smoking with some embers, but it was out.   I was sitting and thinking, like fuck… fuck.. and thinking ok.. one step at a time. And then….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the wind literally shifted&lt;/strong&gt;
I wasn’t even looking at the fire, I had already given up, and there was a fire.  Roaring fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Understanding, that this was indeed divinity stepping in, I immediately started doing the Shiva work.  To make the point even more clear, it started RAINING right as the fire kicked into overdrive from nothing.  Can’t get any clearer then that.  I mean the fire went from nothing, to rain can’t touch me within the span of, maybe 30 seconds.  It was simply not possible for what occured without … ehem &lt;strong&gt;magic&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;we-got-your-back&quot;&gt;We got your back.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I comtemplated this, all I could think about was the idea, that the spirits did have my back.  Really.  While I might not be able to make the lift needed to do the sorcery in this case, they were going to do it from the divinity aspect.  So while there was a ton of blocks, shit worked, casue they helped me.   It was honestly a thing I needed, somewhat having fallen into a existential Nihilism mentality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lots-of-mantras&quot;&gt;Lots of mantras&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I did not have a mala, but I did alot of mantras ( Om Namaha Shivaya).  I clearly heard and understood that what I was asking for 
** the destruction and dissolution of harmful stagnet energies **
was actually being granted.&lt;br /&gt;
In the eye of Shiva, only that which cannot be destroyed remains, and what remains is truth,,,, hahah  ;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a while, I was told to go take care of the things I needed to do in daily life, which was mostly making people food.  Shit did feel different, although not sure.  Energetically, I do feel like alot of stagnet energies got blasted.  Clearly these were a type of talisman destruction, kinda the opposite of the challenge, but whatever… I did something yo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;post-ritual&quot;&gt;Post ritual&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I felt like a large weight removed, but then I still got bad news later in the night which wasnt so bad, but just a sort of trigger, when I was already fried.  Thats a real big problem, although I didn’t fix this website, and I didn’t work on the Comptuer science class I am teaching and was not feeling so good ( so I had to cancel a reading).. I should have worked on more, but what are you going to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I need to start scheduling book time, and more writing time, but alas, 2 jobs is fucking brutal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;before-sleep&quot;&gt;Before Sleep&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did do the object concentration before sleeping ( 10 minutes, with 2 sets of 5).  I am going to try to do more than this.  I am actually finding that it is not so much a focus issue, but physical pain issue.  To that end, I know…  I have to do a more formal plan to somehow fit more excercise in, get to a Chiropractor, and do what I need to.  Going to spend some meditation time, planning that out entirely!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Day 2, High Weidness today.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day 1 - Do Magick for December 2018/ Cleansing rebuilding!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/03/domagick-day-1-december-talismons.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 1 - Do Magick for December 2018/  Cleansing rebuilding!" /><published>2018-12-03T13:35:37-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-03T13:35:37-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/03/domagick-day-1-december-talismons</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/december-2018/2018/12/03/domagick-day-1-december-talismons.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;domagick-day-1&quot;&gt;Domagick Day 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Day 1, December 1, 2018&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;prework&quot;&gt;PreWork&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I decided to ha ve a few harder things with this.   I’ve had alot of death energies around me. &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dropbox.com/s/rd4eblp1oa0advu/starting.md?dl=0&quot;&gt; You can read more about that here &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dropbox.com/s/bz8yd6xux41vjf4/11-14-2018-Death%20to%20Andrieh%20Vitimus.md?dl=0&quot;&gt; More changing&lt;/a&gt;  These are unfinished.   But I kinda decided to just do things in markdown or start coding..   No wordpress nothing like that.  &lt;a href=&quot;http://google.com&quot;&gt;http://google.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Straight only code I develop myself.  Yes oddly this is part of the talisman work.  Reconditing a skill set and accepting it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The plan is to work to get on the excercise program more throughly… Start with 1 Gigong a day and move up to 3-4 sets of gigong a day ( thats only like an hour) with a whole bunch of escalating excercise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortantely for me. I have 2 jobs now ( and one job is very time consuming), it is teaching computer science classes and my day job.   So very little time…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;you got to work with what you got&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;checking-in-with-myself&quot;&gt;Checking in with Myself&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So after the death of my teacher. and a few other things, I had some difficult times even meditating properly.  So I have been doing some major pufication on my holy guardian angel point.  I mean active magic, still can do.. spirit calls, no problem.  But really, Zen style meditation really tells you were you are at.   Simple meditation.  Object concentration on a single point, no thoughts, no distractions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At first, this was painful to even do.   Really painful after the grieving.   But I worked before now to get it up to a hardcore and honest 5 minutes.  I kinda feel into a everything is pointless loop after doing some of the funeral rights.. I was grieving pretty hard for a teacher.  Shit happens.  I will write more on this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;meditation-and-magical-work&quot;&gt;Meditation and Magical Work&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did the meditation outside, did Chilel for 20 minutes with 10 minutes of sitting still with object concentration.  If I was being fully honest,  it was 2 sets of 5  minutes of striaght object concentrations with no thinking.    I did the meditation and gigong outside ( 50 degree weather.   Will do a 3rd set of meditaiton.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the next couple days, will have a full plan down.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Domagick Day 1 Day 1, December 1, 2018</summary></entry></feed>